<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 02:34:31 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 272338<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Thu Aug 27 2020<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Laura, located inland over southern Arkansas.<br/>
<br/>
Showers and thunderstorms associated with a tropical wave over the <br/>
central tropical Atlantic have gradually become a little better <br/>
organized during the day.  Additional development of this system is <br/>
possible during the next several days while it moves westward <br/>
at about 15 mph.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...20 percent.<br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
A tropical wave located over the eastern Atlantic Ocean just west <br/>
of the Cabo Verde Islands is producing disorganized shower and <br/>
thunderstorm activity.  The northern part of this wave, which is <br/>
expected to move rapidly westward over the central Atlantic during <br/>
the next few days, is forecast to remain too far to the north and <br/>
in an unfavorable environment for development to occur.  However, <br/>
the southern part of the wave is expected be nearly stationary <br/>
south of the Cabo Verde Islands for the next several days, and some <br/>
development of this system is possible early next week when it <br/>
begins to move slowly westward over the eastern and central <br/>
tropical Atlantic.<br/>
* Formation chance through 48 hours...low...near 0 percent. <br/>
* Formation chance through 5 days...low...30 percent.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 23:38:57 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202008272338</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Depression Laura (AT3/AL132020)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al132020-202008280234</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 02:34:20 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/280234.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...LAURA WEAKENS TO A DEPRESSION OVER ARKANSAS... ...FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Thu Aug 27
 the center of Laura was located near 35.1, -92.0
 with movement NNE at 15 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 993 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 35 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>35.1, -92.0</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL DEPRESSION</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Laura</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL132020</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Thu Aug 27</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 15 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>993 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>35 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...LAURA WEAKENS TO A DEPRESSION OVER ARKANSAS... ...FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Laura Public Advisory Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

412 
WTNT33 KNHC 280234
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Depression Laura Advisory Number  33
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132020
1000 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020
 
...LAURA WEAKENS TO A DEPRESSION OVER ARKANSAS...
...FLOOD THREAT CONTINUES...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...35.1N 92.0W
ABOUT 30 MI...50 KM NNE OF LITTLE ROCK ARKANSAS
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...35 MPH...55 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 15 DEGREES AT 15 MPH...24 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...993 MB...29.33 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
There are no coastal watches or warnings in effect.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Tropical Depression Laura
was located near latitude 35.1 North, longitude 92.0 West. The
depression is moving toward the north-northeast near 15 mph (24
km/h), and this general motion should continue overnight. 
A northeastward to east-northeastward motion is expected to begin on 
Friday and continue into Saturday.  On the forecast track, the 
center of Laura is forecast to move over Arkansas tonight, the 
mid-Mississippi Valley on Friday, the mid-Atlantic states on 
Saturday, and over the western Atlantic on Sunday.

Maximum sustained winds have decreased to near 35 mph (55 km/h) 
with higher gusts.  Laura is expected to become a remnant low 
pressure system on Saturday, and an extratropical low later this 
weekend.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 993 mb (29.33 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Laura can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3 and WMO header WTNT43 KNHC.
 
RAINFALL: Through Friday, Laura is expected to produce the 
following additional rainfall totals:

Over central and northern Arkansas: Additional 3 to 6 inches.

Over southern Louisiana and southern Mississippi: 1 to 3 inches, 
with isolated additional totals of 5 inches.

Over northern Mississippi, western Tennessee, and south-central to 
southeast Missouri: 1 to 3 inches, with isolated totals of 5 
inches. 

This rainfall will continue to cause widespread flash and urban 
flooding, small streams and creeks to overflow their banks, and 
minor to moderate freshwater river flooding. 

Through Saturday, Laura is expected to produce 1 to 3 inches with 
isolated maximum amounts of 5 inches across portions of the
Tennessee and Lower Ohio Valleys, the central and southern 
Appalachians, and the Mid-Atlantic States. This rainfall may lead to 
flash and urban flooding and rapid rises on small streams.

TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes remain possible this evening across
eastern Arkansas, western Tennessee, northern Mississippi, and the
Missouri Bootheel.  The risk for a few tornadoes is expected to
redevelop Friday afternoon into the evening across parts of the
Mid-South and Tennessee Valley regions.
 
SURF:  Swells produced by Laura continue to affect the U.S. Gulf
coast from the Florida Panhandle to Texas.  These swells are likely
to cause life-threatening surf and rip current conditions.  Please
consult products from your local weather office.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
This is the last public advisory issued by the National Hurricane
Center on this system.  Future information on this system can be 
found in Public Advisories issued by the Weather Prediction Center 
beginning at 4 AM CDT, under AWIPS header TCPAT3, WMO header 
WTNT33 KWNH, and on the web at http://www.wpc.ncep.noaa.gov. 
 
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 02:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/280234.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/280234.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Laura Forecast Advisory Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI AUG 28 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

410 
WTNT23 KNHC 280234
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION LAURA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  33
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132020
0300 UTC FRI AUG 28 2020
 
THERE ARE NO COASTAL WATCHES OR WARNINGS IN EFFECT.
 
TROPICAL DEPRESSION CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.1N  92.0W AT 28/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  15 DEGREES AT  13 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  993 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  30 KT WITH GUSTS TO  40 KT.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 35.1N  92.0W AT 28/0300Z
AT 28/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 34.4N  92.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 36.3N  91.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0000Z 37.3N  87.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1200Z 38.0N  82.3W...POST-TROP/INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0000Z 38.5N  75.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1200Z 41.5N  67.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...  0NE  90SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/0000Z 44.0N  60.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  60SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 01/0000Z 48.0N  52.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 02/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 35.1N  92.0W
 
THIS IS THE LAST FORECAST/ADVISORY ISSUED BY THE NATIONAL HURRICANE 
CENTER ON THIS SYSTEM.  FUTURE INFORMATION ON THIS SYSTEM CAN BE 
FOUND IN PUBLIC ADVISORIES ISSUED BY THE WEATHER PREDICTION CENTER 
BEGINNING AT 4 AM CDT, UNDER AWIPS HEADER TCPAT3, WMO HEADER 
WTNT33 KWNH, AND ON THE WEB AT HTTP://WWW.WPC.NCEP.NOAA.GOV. 
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 02:34:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/280234.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/280234.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Laura Forecast Discussion Number 32</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 272043
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Laura Discussion Number  32
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL132020
400 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020
 
Laura has continued to weaken this afternoon.  The satellite and
radar presentation of the tropical cyclone has continued to degrade,
and the center has now moved into southern Arkansas.  The initial
intensity has been reduced to 45 kt, and is based on a blend of
surface observations, Doppler radar data, and typical over land 
tropical cyclone filling rates.  Sustained tropical storm force
winds have been observed in northern Louisiana, and wind gusts to
nearly 50 kt were reported in southern Arkansas earlier this
afternoon.
 
Laura will continue to rapidly weaken during the next 6-12 hours,
and it is expected to become a tropical depression either this
evening or overnight.  The extratropical remnants could strengthen
over the western Atlantic early next week, and the track and
intensity forecast for that time is based on guidance from
the NOAA Ocean Prediction Center.
 
The tropical storm has turned north-northeastward or 015/13 kt.
The cyclone is forecast to turn northeastward, and then east-
northeastward as it becomes embedded within the mid-latitude
westerlies on Friday.  This motion will take Laura or its remnants
across the central Appalachians and to the Mid-Atlantic states on
Saturday.  After that time, the system should accelerate
east-northeastward to northeastward over the western Atlantic.  The
updated NHC track forecast remains similar to the previous advisory
and is close to the various consensus models.
 
Key Messages:
 
1. Tropical storm force winds, especially in gusts, will continue
near the center of Laura over portions of extreme northern Louisiana
and Arkansas this evening.
 
2. Flash flooding along small streams, urban areas, and roadways
will continue across portions of Louisiana, Mississippi and
Arkansas.  Additional rainfall will also lead to minor to moderate
freshwater river flooding.  The heavy rainfall threat and flash and
urban flooding potential will spread northeastward into the
middle-Mississippi, lower Ohio and Tennessee Valleys, and
Mid-Atlantic States Friday and Saturday.
 
3. A few tornadoes are possible this evening across central and
eastern Arkansas into Mississippi.  The risk for a few tornadoes
should redevelop Friday afternoon and evening across parts of the
Mid-South and Tennessee Valley regions.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  27/2100Z 33.4N  92.8W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 12H  28/0600Z 35.3N  91.7W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 24H  28/1800Z 36.7N  89.3W   25 KT  30 MPH...INLAND
 36H  29/0600Z 37.4N  85.1W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 48H  29/1800Z 38.2N  78.6W   25 KT  30 MPH...POST-TROP/INLAND
 60H  30/0600Z 39.6N  70.9W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 72H  30/1800Z 43.1N  63.4W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  31/1800Z 48.8N  50.7W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  01/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 20:43:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/272043.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/272043.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Laura Wind Speed Probabilities Number 33</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI AUG 28 2020                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT3 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
TROPICAL DEPRESSION LAURA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  33       
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL132020               
0300 UTC FRI AUG 28 2020                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL DEPRESSION LAURA WAS LOCATED NEAR   
LATITUDE 35.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 92.0 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 30 KTS...35 MPH...55 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z FRI 12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 00Z MON 00Z TUE 00Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HIBERNIA OILFD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAPE RACE NFLD 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   X(13)
CAPE RACE NFLD 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
ILE ST PIERRE  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   X(10)
 
BURGEO NFLD    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
PTX BASQUES    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
SYDNEY NS      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)
 
SABLE ISLAND   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   5(16)   X(16)
 
HALIFAX NS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
YARMOUTH NS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 02:34:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Depression Laura Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235046.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132020_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Laura 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Thu, 27 Aug 2020 23:50:46 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235046.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT13/AL132020_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Depression Laura 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Thu, 27 Aug 2020 21:24:41 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 23:50:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235046.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/235046.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for New Orleans / Baton Rouge, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  410 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 21:10:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  425 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 21:25:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jackson, MS</title>
<description>Issued at  434 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 21:34:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Little Rock, AR</title>
<description>Issued at  452 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 21:52:22 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLZK.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLZK.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Shreveport, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  654 PM CDT Thu Aug 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2020 23:54:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KSHV.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KSHV.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
