<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
   <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
   <description>Simulated NHC Forecast/Advisories</description>
   <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
   <copyright>2015 Jason Fleming</copyright>
   <managingEditor>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</managingEditor>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <webMaster>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</webMaster>
   <image>
      <url>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/seahorse.png</url>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
      <description>Seahorse</description>
      <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
      <width>96</width>
      <height>128</height>
   </image>
   <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm BARRY Forecast/Advisory Number 5</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC THU JUL 11 2019 <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT2 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM

TROPICAL STORM BARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   5
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022019
1500 UTC THU JUL 11 2019

CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS NOW IN EFFECT FOR THE LOUISIANA COAST
FROM THE MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER TO MORGAN CITY.

A STORM SURGE WARNING IS NOW IN EFFECT FOR THE LOUISIANA COAST FROM
THE MOUTH OF THE ATCHAFALAYA RIVER TO SHELL BEACH.

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS NOW IN EFFECT FOR THE MISSISSIPPI COAST
EAST OF THE MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA
BORDER...AND FOR LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN AND LAKE MAUREPAS INCLUDING
METROPOLITAN NEW ORLEANS.

A STORM SURGE WATCH IS NOW IN EFFECT FOR THE MISSISSIPPI COAST FROM
THE MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER TO MORGAN CITY

A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE ATCHAFALAYA RIVER TO SHELL BEACH

A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SHELL BEACH TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER
* MOUTH OF THE ATCHAFALAYA RIVER TO INTRACOASTAL CITY

A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER TO CAMERON

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EAST OF THE MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA
BORDER
* LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN AND LAKE MAUREPAS INCLUDING METROPOLITAN NEW
ORLEANS

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.

A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE DURING
THE NEXT 36 HOURS IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF
AREAS AT RISK PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE
WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV. THIS IS A
LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION. PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS
SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM
RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.
PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL
OFFICIALS.

A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC AVAILABLE AT
HURRICANES.GOV.

A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.

ADDITIONAL WATCHES AND WARNINGS MAY BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THE
NORTHERN GULF COAST LATER TODAY OR TONIGHT. INTERESTS ELSEWHERE
ALONG THE GULF COAST FROM THE UPPER TEXAS COAST TO THE FLORIDA
PANHANDLE SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM.

TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.8N  88.7W AT 11/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  40 NM

PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 270 DEGREES AT   4 KT

ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1005 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......  0NE  80SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.

REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.8N  88.7W AT 11/1500Z
AT 11/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 27.7N  88.5W

FORECAST VALID 12/0000Z 27.8N  89.3W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 80NE  80SE   0SW   0NW.

FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 28.1N  90.0W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 90NE  90SE   0SW   0NW.

FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 28.6N  90.8W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  70SW  60NW.

FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 29.4N  91.4W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  70SW  60NW.

FORECAST VALID 14/1200Z 32.0N  91.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.

EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY

OUTLOOK VALID 15/1200Z 34.5N  91.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.

OUTLOOK VALID 16/1200Z 37.0N  89.5W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.

REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 27.8N  88.7W

INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 11/1800Z

NEXT ADVISORY AT 11/2100Z

$$
FORECASTER BEVEN

</pre>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2019/02/05.022019.index-at.xml</link>
      <guid>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2019/02/05.022019.index-at.xml</guid>
      <author>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</author>
   </item>
</channel>
</rss>
