<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
   <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
   <description>Simulated NHC Forecast/Advisories</description>
   <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
   <copyright>2015 Jason Fleming</copyright>
   <managingEditor>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</managingEditor>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <webMaster>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</webMaster>
   <image>
      <url>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/seahorse.png</url>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
      <description>Seahorse</description>
      <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
      <width>96</width>
      <height>128</height>
   </image>
   <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm BARRY Forecast/Advisory Number 7</title>
      <description>Issued at 0300 UTC FRI JUL 12 2019 <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT2 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM CCA

TROPICAL STORM BARRY FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   7...CORRECTED
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL022019
0300 UTC FRI JUL 12 2019

CORRECTED STORM SURGE WATCH SECTION

CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...

THE STORM SURGE WARNING HAS BEEN EXTENDED WESTWARD TO INTRACOASTAL
CITY.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...

A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* INTRACOASTAL CITY TO GRAND ISLE

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER TO GRAND ISLE
* LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN AND LAKE MAUREPAS INCLUDING METROPOLITAN NEW
ORLEANS
* INTRACOASTAL CITY TO CAMERON

A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* INTRACOASTAL CITY TO SHELL BEACH

A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SHELL BEACH TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER
* LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN

A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER TO GRAND ISLE
* INTRACOASTAL CITY TO CAMERON

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EAST OF THE MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA
BORDER

A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.

A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE
DURING THE NEXT 36 HOURS IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS.  FOR A
DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC AVAILABLE AT
HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION.  PERSONS
LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS TO
PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR
OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER
INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.

A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 HOURS.

A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.

INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE GULF COAST FROM THE UPPER TEXAS COAST
TO THE FLORIDA PANHANDLE SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF THIS SYSTEM.

TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.9N  89.4W AT 12/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM

PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST OR 275 DEGREES AT   3 KT

ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1001 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  45 KT WITH GUSTS TO  55 KT.
34 KT....... 70NE 120SE 120SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE  60SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.

REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 27.9N  89.4W AT 12/0300Z
AT 12/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 27.8N  89.2W

FORECAST VALID 12/1200Z 28.0N  89.9W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  60SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 80NE 120SE 120SW   0NW.

FORECAST VALID 13/0000Z 28.5N  90.7W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT... 90NE 120SE  90SW  60NW.

FORECAST VALID 13/1200Z 29.5N  91.5W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  40SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE 120SE  70SW  60NW.

FORECAST VALID 14/0000Z 30.5N  91.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE 120SE  60SW   0NW.

FORECAST VALID 15/0000Z 33.2N  92.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.

EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY

OUTLOOK VALID 16/0000Z 35.7N  91.2W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.

OUTLOOK VALID 17/0000Z 38.2N  87.9W...POST-TROP/REMNT LOW
MAX WIND  15 KT...GUSTS  20 KT.

REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 27.9N  89.4W

INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT32 KNHC/MIATCPAT2...AT 12/0600Z

NEXT ADVISORY AT 12/0900Z

$$
FORECASTER BROWN

</pre>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2019/02/07.022019.index-at.xml</link>
      <guid>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2019/02/07.022019.index-at.xml</guid>
      <author>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</author>
   </item>
</channel>
</rss>
