<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
   <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
   <description>Simulated NHC Forecast/Advisories</description>
   <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
   <copyright>2015 Jason Fleming</copyright>
   <managingEditor>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</managingEditor>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <webMaster>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</webMaster>
   <image>
      <url>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/seahorse.png</url>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
      <description>Seahorse</description>
      <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
      <width>96</width>
      <height>128</height>
   </image>
   <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm ISAAC Forecast/Advisory Number 23</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC SUN AUG 26 2012 <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM CCC
 
TROPICAL STORM ISAAC FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  23...CORRECTED
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092012
2100 UTC SUN AUG 26 2012

CORRECTED TROPICAL STORM WARNING AREA FOR FLORIDA PANHANDLE
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF THE BAHAMAS HAS DISCONTINUED THE TROPICAL STORM
WARNING FOR THE NORTHWESTERN BAHAMAS.
 
THE GOVERNMENT OF CUBA HAS DISCONTINUED ALL WATCHES AND WARNINGS.
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH FROM NORTH OF SEBASTIAN INLET TO FLAGLER
BEACH IS DISCONTINUED.
 
THE HURRICANE WARNING IS CHANGED TO A TROPICAL STORM WARNING FOR THE
FLORIDA KEYS INCLUDING THE DRY TORTUGAS AND FLORIDA BAY.
 
THE HURRICANE WARNING FOR THE WEST COAST OF FLORIDA FROM BONITA
BEACH SOUTHWARD TO OCEAN REEF IS CHANGED TO A TROPICAL STORM
WARNING.
 
THE TROPICAL STROM WARNING ALONG THE FLORIDA PANHANDLE HAS BEEN
EXTENDED WESTWARD TO EAST OF DESTIN. 

THE HURRICANE WATCH IS CHANGED TO A HURRICANE WARNING FOR THE
NORTHERN GULF OF MEXICO COAST FROM EAST OF MORGAN CITY LOUSIANA TO
DESTIN FLORIDA...INCLUDING METROPOLITAN NEW ORLEANS...LAKE
PONTCHARTRAIN...AND LAKE MAUREPAS.
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING FROM SUWANNEE RIVER TO TARPON SPRINGS IS
DISCONTINUED.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EAST OF MORGAN CITY LOUISIANA TO DESTIN FLORIDA...INCLUDING
METROPOLITAN NEW ORLEANS...LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...AND LAKE MAUREPAS
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EAST OF DESTIN TO INDIAN PASS FLORIDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* THE FLORIDA PENINSULA FROM SEBASTIAN INLET SOUTHWARD ON THE EAST
COAST AND FROM TARPON SPRINGS SOUTHWARD ON THE WEST COAST.
* FLORIDA KEYS...INCLUDING THE DRY TORTUGAS AND FLORIDA BAY
* LAKE OKEECHOBEE
* EAST OF DESTIN FLORIDA TO THE SUWANNEE RIVER
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 24
HOURS. PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED
TO COMPLETION.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA. A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
  
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.2N  82.3W AT 26/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  25 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE WEST-NORTHWEST OR 295 DEGREES AT  14 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  50 KT WITH GUSTS TO  60 KT.
50 KT....... 60NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
34 KT.......180NE 120SE  80SW 180NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 150SE 120SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 24.2N  82.3W AT 26/2100Z
AT 26/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 23.9N  81.5W
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0600Z 25.1N  83.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
34 KT...180NE 120SE  80SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1800Z 26.3N  85.9W
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 60NE   0SE   0SW  60NW.
34 KT...180NE 120SE  80SW 180NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 27.7N  87.6W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE  10SW  20NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...180NE 150SE  80SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1800Z 28.9N  88.5W
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
50 KT... 70NE  60SE  50SW  60NW.
34 KT...180NE 150SE  90SW 160NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 30.7N  89.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
50 KT... 60NE  70SE  60SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 150SE 100SW  90NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 175 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 225 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 20 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/1800Z 32.5N  90.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 31/1800Z 34.5N  90.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 24.2N  82.3W
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 27/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH

</pre>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2012 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2012/09/23.092012.index-at.xml</link>
      <guid>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2012/09/23.092012.index-at.xml</guid>
      <author>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</author>
   </item>
</channel>
</rss>
