<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 14:48:54 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 261144<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Mon Oct 26 2020<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Zeta, located over the northwestern Caribbean Sea.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Roberts<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 11:44:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202010261144</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Zeta (AT3/AL282020)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al282020-202010261448</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 14:48:50 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/261448.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE LIKELY OVER PORTIONS OF THE YUCATAN PENINSULA BY LATE TODAY...
 As of 10:00 AM CDT Mon Oct 26
 the center of Zeta was located near 19.1, -85.3
 with movement NW at 10 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 992 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 70 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.1, -85.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Zeta</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL282020</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM CDT Mon Oct 26</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 10 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>992 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>70 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE LIKELY OVER PORTIONS OF THE YUCATAN PENINSULA BY LATE TODAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Public Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 261448
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Zeta Advisory Number   8
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
1000 AM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020
 
...HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE LIKELY OVER
PORTIONS OF THE YUCATAN PENINSULA BY LATE TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 AM CDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.1N 85.3W
ABOUT 140 MI...230 KM SE OF COZUMEL MEXICO
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...70 MPH...110 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 10 MPH...17 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...992 MB...29.29 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
None.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Tulum to Dzilam Mexico
* Cozumel
 
 A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Pinar del Rio Cuba
* South of Tulum to Punta Allen
* West of Dzilam to Progreso
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm- 
force winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or 
dangerous.  Preparations to protect life and property should be 
rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
Watches will likely be required for a portion of the northern Gulf
Coast later today.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM CDT (1500 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Zeta was
located near latitude 19.1 North, longitude 85.3 West.  Zeta is
moving toward the northwest near 10 mph (17 km/h).  A northwestward
motion with some increase in forward speed is expected over the
next day or so, followed by a turn toward the north Tuesday night.
A faster northward to north-northeastward motion is forecast on
Wednesday.  On the forecast track, the center of Zeta will move near
or over the northern Yucatan Peninsula later today or tonight, move
over the southern Gulf of Mexico on Tuesday, and approach the
northern Gulf Coast on Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 70 mph (110 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Strengthening is forecast, and Zeta is expected to become
a hurricane later today.  Some weakening is likely while Zeta
moves over the Yucatan Peninsula tonight and early Tuesday.  Zeta
is forecast to strengthen again while it moves over the southern
Gulf of Mexico later on Tuesday
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 992 mb (29.29 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Zeta can be found in the Tropical Cyclone 
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43
KNHC, and on the web at <a href="http://www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml">www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml</a>.
 
RAINFALL:  Rainfall totals of 4 to 8 inches with local amounts of 12
inches are possible through Tuesday along and east-northeast of
Zeta's track across the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico, the Cayman
Islands, and central to western Cuba.
 
Heavy rains will begin to impact the central Gulf Coast Tuesday
night, spreading inland across eastern Mississippi, Alabama,
northern Georgia during Wednesday, through the southern Appalachians
Wednesday night and into the Mid-Atlantic on Thursday.  Rainfall
totals of 2 to 4 inches with isolated amounts of 6 inches are
expected across these areas, resulting in flash, urban, small
stream, and minor river flooding.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane
Warning area in the Yucatan Peninsula by late today.  Tropical
storm conditions are expected within the Tropical Storm Warning
area in Mexico by late today.  Tropical storm conditions could occur
in the warning area in western Cuba beginning later today.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge will raise water levels by
as much as 2 to 4 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate
coast in the Hurricane Warning area near and to the north of where
the center makes landfall in the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 14:48:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/261448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/261448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Forecast Advisory Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON OCT 26 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 261448
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM ZETA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   8
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020
1500 UTC MON OCT 26 2020
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* TULUM TO DZILAM MEXICO
* COZUMEL
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PINAR DEL RIO CUBA
* SOUTH OF TULUM TO PUNTA ALLEN
* WEST OF DZILAM TO PROGRESO
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
WATCHES WILL LIKELY BE REQUIRED FOR A PORTION OF THE NORTHERN GULF
COAST LATER TODAY.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.1N  85.3W AT 26/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT   9 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  992 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT.......  0NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT....... 60NE 100SE   0SW   0NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE  60SE  30SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.1N  85.3W AT 26/1500Z
AT 26/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 18.9N  84.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 20.1N  86.7W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  50SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT... 90NE 100SE  30SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 21.5N  88.8W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT... 90NE  90SE  30SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 23.3N  90.8W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 25.7N  91.8W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 20NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE   0SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  40SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0000Z 28.9N  90.7W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
50 KT... 40NE  40SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE 110SE  40SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1200Z 33.0N  87.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  40SE  40SW   0NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 30/1200Z 40.0N  73.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
 
OUTLOOK VALID 31/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.1N  85.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 26/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 26/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 14:48:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/261448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/261448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Forecast Discussion Number 7</title>
<description>Issued at 500 AM EDT Mon Oct 26 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 260853
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Zeta Discussion Number   7
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
500 AM EDT Mon Oct 26 2020
 
Zeta's satellite presentation has continued to improve overnight. 
The cold convective cloud shield has expanded northwestward over the 
center and there has been a continued increase in banding over the 
southern and southeastern portions of the circulation. With the 
expansion of the convection over the center, it appears that a CDO 
feature is trying to form. A NOAA P-3 reconnaissance aircraft that 
has been investigating Zeta overnight has reported that the pressure 
has fallen to 990 mb.  The aircraft has found peak 850-mb 
flight-level winds of 69 kt and believable SFMR winds of around 60 
kt, with some higher flagged values.  These data support increasing 
the initial intensity to 60 kt for this advisory.
 
Recent aircraft fixes indicate that Zeta has begun its expected 
northwestward motion at about 315 degrees at 8 kt.  The storm should 
begin to move at an even faster pace toward the northwest as a 
mid-level ridge builds over the western Atlantic and Florida during 
the next 24 to 36 hours. This ridge will steer Zeta across the 
northern portion of the Yucatan peninsula tonight, and over the 
south-central Gulf of Mexico on Tuesday.  A vigorous mid- to 
upper-level trough currently over the western United States is 
forecast to begin ejecting out of the southwestern U.S. by mid-week, 
which will erode the western portion of the aforementioned ridge.  
This should cause Zeta to accelerate northward and approach the 
northern Gulf of Mexico on Wednesday.  The 0000 UTC global models, 
which incorporated dropwindsonde data from the earlier NOAA G-IV 
synoptic surveillance mission, have come into somewhat better 
agreement this cycle.  While there is still some spread on exactly 
when the northward turn takes place and how quickly Zeta accelerates 
north-northeastward over the Gulf of Mexico, the cross-track spread 
at 60 h is about half of what it was before, resulting in an 
increase in track-forecast confidence.  The latest NHC track is in 
best agreement with the GFS ensemble mean and the GFEX consensus 
aid.  This is a little right of the TVCA and HCCA multi-model 
consensus, but quite close to the previous NHC track forecast.
 
With the recent improvement in the outflow over Zeta, it appears 
that the shear that had prevented strengthening has abated.  The 
shear ahead of the storm is expected to remain low while the cyclone 
traverses the deep, warm water of the northwestern Caribbean Sea. 
As a result, Zeta is forecast to become a hurricane this morning, 
and continued strengthening is likely until Zeta moves over the 
Yucatan peninsula this evening. The landfall intensity is likely to 
be a little stronger than shown below since Zeta will be inland over 
the Yucatan peninsula by the 24-hour forecast point.  Environmental 
conditions over the southern Gulf of Mexico are forecast to be 
conducive for some re-strengthening as Zeta moves over the 
south-central Gulf on Tuesday.  Increasing shear and the cooler 
shelf waters of the northern Gulf are likely to result in some 
reduction in intensity before Zeta reaches the northern Gulf coast. 

KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Hurricane conditions and storm surge are expected in portions of
the northern Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico tonight and early Tuesday.
Tropical storm conditions could occur over extreme western Cuba
beginning later today.
 
2. Through Tuesday, heavy rainfall is expected from Zeta across the 
Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico, the Cayman Islands, and central to 
western Cuba. This rainfall may lead to flash flooding in urban 
areas.  
 
3. Zeta is forecast to be at or near hurricane strength when it 
approaches the northern Gulf Coast on Wednesday, and there is an 
increasing risk of storm surge, rainfall, and wind impacts from 
Louisiana to the Florida Panhandle. Residents in these areas should 
monitor the progress of Zeta and updates to the forecast.
 
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  26/0900Z 18.7N  84.3W   60 KT  70 MPH
 12H  26/1800Z 19.5N  85.5W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  27/0600Z 20.8N  87.5W   75 KT  85 MPH...INLAND
 36H  27/1800Z 22.5N  89.6W   65 KT  75 MPH...OVER WATER
 48H  28/0600Z 24.7N  91.1W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  28/1800Z 27.7N  90.8W   65 KT  75 MPH
 72H  29/0600Z 31.8N  88.2W   45 KT  50 MPH...INLAND
 96H  30/0600Z 39.0N  75.5W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  31/0600Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 08:53:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/260853.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/260853.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Wind Speed Probabilities Number 8</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON OCT 26 2020                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 261448
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ZETA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   8             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020               
1500 UTC MON OCT 26 2020                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ZETA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
19.1 NORTH...LONGITUDE 85.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
60 KTS...70 MPH...110 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z MON AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z MON 00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
ISLIP NY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
NYC CNTRL PARK 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
NWS EARLE NJ   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)
WALLOPS CDA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   6(11)   X(11)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   1(12)   X(12)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   2(20)   X(20)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   6(14)   X(14)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   2(12)   X(12)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   4(19)   X(19)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)   2(25)   X(25)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  25(25)   2(27)   X(27)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  19(21)   X(21)   X(21)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  34(34)   2(36)   X(36)
MOBILE AL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
MOBILE AL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  39(40)   1(41)   X(41)
GULFPORT MS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
GULFPORT MS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  42(43)   1(44)   X(44)
STENNIS MS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)   X(12)
STENNIS MS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  46(48)   1(49)   X(49)
BURAS LA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
BURAS LA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)  35(46)   1(47)   X(47)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
GFMX 280N 890W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
JACKSON MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  41(43)   X(43)   X(43)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   X(14)   X(14)
NEW ORLEANS LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  22(25)  45(70)   X(70)   X(70)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  30(33)   X(33)   X(33)
GFMX 280N 910W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  24(25)   X(25)   X(25)
BATON ROUGE LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
BATON ROUGE LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  33(35)   X(35)   X(35)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)   X(12)
MORGAN CITY LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)   X(17)   X(17)
LAFAYETTE LA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  18(20)   X(20)   X(20)
NEW IBERIA LA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
NEW IBERIA LA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)  14(31)   X(31)   X(31)
GFMX 280N 930W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   7(10)   X(10)   X(10)
GFMX 280N 930W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   7(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MERIDA MX      34  1  13(14)   8(22)   1(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
MERIDA MX      50  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
COZUMEL MX     34 69  27(96)   1(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
COZUMEL MX     50 25  41(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)   X(66)
COZUMEL MX     64 11  28(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GUANAJA        34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  4   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PENSACOLA NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  28(28)   1(29)   X(29)
PENSACOLA NAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
KEESLER AB     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  43(44)   1(45)   X(45)
KEESLER AB     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)   X(13)
KEESLER AB     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 14:48:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/261448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/261448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115424.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 26 Oct 2020 11:54:24 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115424.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 26 Oct 2020 09:25:23 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 11:54:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115424.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/115424.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
