<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 02:46:50 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 262317<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 PM EDT Mon Oct 26 2020<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on recently <br/>
upgraded Hurricane Zeta, located over the northwestern Caribbean <br/>
Sea.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Reinhart/Cangialosi<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 23:18:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202010262318</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Zeta (AT3/AL282020)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al282020-202010261910</guid>
 <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 19:10:07 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS LASHING YUCATAN... ...ZETA SHOULD MAKE LANDFALL IN A COUPLE OF HOURS WITH HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE...
 As of 10:00 PM CDT Mon Oct 26
 the center of Zeta was located near 20.2, -87.1
 with movement NW at 13 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 982 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 80 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>20.2, -87.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>HURRICANE</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Zeta</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL282020</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 PM CDT Mon Oct 26</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 13 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>982 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>80 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS LASHING YUCATAN... ...ZETA SHOULD MAKE LANDFALL IN A COUPLE OF HOURS WITH HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Public Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 PM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCPAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Zeta Advisory Number  10
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
1000 PM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020
 
...STRONG WINDS AND HEAVY RAINS LASHING YUCATAN...
...ZETA SHOULD MAKE LANDFALL IN A COUPLE OF HOURS WITH HURRICANE
CONDITIONS AND A DANGEROUS STORM SURGE...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 PM CDT...0300 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...20.2N 87.1W
ABOUT 25 MI...40 KM E OF TULUM MEXICO
ABOUT 625 MI...1010 KM SSE OF THE MOUTH OF THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...80 MPH...130 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 13 MPH...20 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...982 MB...29.00 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

None
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Punta Allen to Progreso Mexico
* Cozumel
 
A Storm Surge Watch is in effect for...
* Intracoastal City Louisiana to Navarre Florida
* Lake Borgne, Lake Pontchartrain, Vermilion Bay, Pensacola Bay, and
Mobile Bay
 
A Hurricane Watch is in effect for...
* Morgan City Louisiana to the Mississippi/Alabama border
* Lake Pontchartrain, Lake Maurepas, and Metropolitan New Orleans
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Mississippi/Alabama border to Okaloosa/Walton County Line Florida
* West of Morgan City to Intracoastal City Louisiana
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area, in this case within the next 6
hours.
 
A Storm Surge Watch means there is a possibility of life-
threatening inundation, from rising water moving inland from the
coastline, in the indicated locations during the next 48 hours.
For a depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.
 
A Hurricane Watch means that hurricane conditions are possible
within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 PM CDT (0300 UTC), the center of Hurricane Zeta was located 
near latitude 20.2 North, longitude 87.1 West. Zeta is moving toward 
the northwest near 13 mph (20 km/h), and this general motion is 
forecast during the next day or so. Zeta should turn toward the 
north Tuesday night, and a faster northward to north-northeastward 
motion is anticipated on Wednesday. On the forecast track, the 
center of Zeta will move over the northern Yucatan Peninsula during 
the next couple of hours, move over the southern Gulf of Mexico on 
Tuesday, and approach the northern Gulf Coast in the watch area on 
Wednesday.
 
Maximum sustained winds remain near 80 mph (130 km/h) with higher 
gusts.  Some slight strengthening is possible before Zeta makes 
landfall in the Yucatan Peninsula.  Weakening is forecast while Zeta 
moves over the Yucatan Peninsula late tonight and early Tuesday.  
Zeta is forecast to re-strengthen when it moves over the southern 
Gulf of Mexico later on Tuesday and be at or near hurricane strength 
when it approaches the northern Gulf Coast on Wednesday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 45 miles (75 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles
(220 km).  A Weatherflow station just south of Playa del Carmen 
reported sustained winds of 67 mph (108 km/h) with a gust to 87 mph 
(140 km/h). Another Weatherflow station in Cancun recently reported 
sustained winds of 60 mph (97 km/h) with a gust to 72 mph (116 
km/h). 
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 982 mb (29.00 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Zeta can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43
KNHC, and on the web at www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
STORM SURGE:  A dangerous storm surge will raise water levels by
as much as 2 to 4 feet above normal tide levels along the immediate
coast in the Hurricane Warning area near and to the north of where
the center makes landfall in the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
The combination of a dangerous storm surge and the tide will cause
normally dry areas near the coast to be flooded by rising waters
moving inland from the shoreline.  The water could reach the
following heights above ground somewhere in the indicated areas if
the peak surge occurs at the time of high tide...
 
Port Fourchon LA to Dauphin Island AL including Lake Borgne...4-6
ft
Intracoastal City LA to Port Fourchon LA including Vermilion
Bay...2-4 ft
Dauphin Island AL to Navarre FL including Mobile Bay and Pensacola
Bay...2-4 ft
Lake Pontchartrain...2-4 ft
Navarre FL to Yankeetown FL including Choctawhatchee Bay and Saint
Andrew Bay...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle,
and can vary greatly over short distances.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
RAINFALL:  Rainfall totals of 4 to 8 inches with local amounts of 12 
inches are possible through Tuesday along and east-northeast of 
Zeta’s track across the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico and the Cayman 
Islands. An additional 1 to 3 inches of rain will be possible across 
western Cuba through Tuesday.

An initial area of heavy rains will begin to impact the central Gulf 
Coast Tuesday night, spreading north into the Tennessee Valley on 
Wednesday.  The core of the heavy rains associated with Zeta will 
push northeast from eastern Louisiana, across southern Mississippi, 
Alabama, northern Georgia through Wednesday night, and through the 
southern Appalachians into the Mid-Atlantic on Thursday.  Rainfall 
totals of 2 to 4 inches with isolated amounts of 6 inches are 
expected across these areas, resulting in flash, urban, small 
stream, and minor river flooding.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are already occurring within the 
Hurricane Warning area and should continue for the next several 
hours.
 
Hurricane conditions are possible within the Hurricane Watch area on
the northern Gulf Coast late Wednesday, and tropical storm
conditions are possible within the Tropical Storm Watch area on the
northern Gulf Coast late Wednesday.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 AM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 AM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Blake
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 02:46:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Forecast Advisory Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 270246
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE ZETA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  10
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020
0300 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUNTA ALLEN TO PROGRESO MEXICO
* COZUMEL
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* INTRACOASTAL CITY LOUISIANA TO NAVARRE FLORIDA
* LAKE BORGNE...LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...VERMILION BAY...PENSACOLA
BAY...AND MOBILE BAY
 
A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MORGAN CITY LOUISIANA TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER
* LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...LAKE MAUREPAS...AND METROPOLITAN NEW ORLEANS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER TO OKALOOSA/WALTON COUNTY LINE FLORIDA
* WEST OF MORGAN CITY TO INTRACOASTAL CITY LOUISIANA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 6
HOURS.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE...IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT
HURRICANES.GOV.
 
A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.2N  87.1W AT 27/0300Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  982 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 40NE  40SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 70NE  70SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT.......120NE 110SE  60SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..120NE  90SE  30SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 20.2N  87.1W AT 27/0300Z
AT 27/0000Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.9N  86.6W
 
FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 21.3N  88.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...130NE 100SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 23.1N  90.7W...OVER WATER
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 20NE   0SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  40SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 110SE  30SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 25.6N  91.6W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...110NE 120SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0000Z 29.1N  90.1W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1200Z 33.8N  85.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT... 40NE  60SE  50SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0000Z 38.5N  76.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE 150SE 150SW  30NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 31/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 20.2N  87.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 27/0600Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 27/0900Z
 
$$
FORECASTER BLAKE

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 02:46:30 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/270246.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/270246.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Forecast Discussion Number 9</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 262049
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Zeta Discussion Number   9
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
400 PM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020

The cloud pattern of Zeta became better organized today, with deep 
convection forming over and around the center and some banding 
features developing.  The Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunters 
recently found surface winds to near 70 kt over the inner 
northeastern quadrant of the circulation and a central pressure of 
around 981 mb, signifying that the system had become a hurricane.  
Given the increased organization over very warm waters, some 
additional strengthening is possible before the center crosses the 
east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula this evening.  Some weakening 
should occur while Zeta interacts with land tonight and early 
Tuesday.  Once the center moves into the southern Gulf of Mexico 
tomorrow, atmospheric and oceanic conditions are conducive for some 
re-strengthening.  When Zeta moves over the northern Gulf of Mexico 
later on Wednesday, cooler shelf waters and some increase in 
southwesterly shear should halt the intensification process, with 
some weakening possible by the time the center reaches the northern 
Gulf Coast, but Zeta is still expected to be at or near hurricane 
intensity at landfall. The NHC intensity forecast is similar to the 
previous one and is near or above the model consensus.

The hurricane continues to move on a generally northwestward track, 
or at about 305/10 kt.  There are basically no changes to the track 
forecast reasoning, or to the forecast itself.  For the next couple 
of days, Zeta should move around the southwestern and western 
periphery of a mid-level high pressure area centered just east of 
Florida.  Thereafter, a shortwave trough approaching from the west 
is likely to cause the cyclone to accelerate north-northeastward to 
northeastward and move over the southeastern and eastern United 
States.  The system should move off the northeast U.S. coast and 
become an extratropical cyclone within the next 4 days.  The 
guidance has come into better agreement since yesterday, and the 
official track forecast is very close to the corrected model 
consensus, HCCA.

Storm Surge, Hurricane, and Tropical Storm Watches have been issued 
for a portion of the northern U.S. Gulf Coast.

KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. Hurricane conditions and dangerous storm surge are expected in 
portions of the northern Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico this evening 
through early Tuesday.  Through Tuesday, heavy rainfall is expected 
across the Yucatan Peninsula, the Cayman Islands, and central to 
western Cuba, which could lead to flash flooding in urban areas.  

2. Hurricane conditions and life-threatening storm surge are 
possible along portions of the northern Gulf Coast on Wednesday, and 
Storm Surge and Hurricane Watches are in effect. Residents in the 
watch areas should follow any advice given by local officials. 

3. Between Tuesday night and Thursday, heavy rainfall is expected 
from portions of the central Gulf Coast into the southern 
Appalachians and Mid-Atlantic States near and in advance of Zeta. 
This rainfall will lead to flash, urban, small stream, and minor 
river flooding.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  26/2100Z 19.5N  86.0W   70 KT  80 MPH
 12H  27/0600Z 20.5N  87.7W   75 KT  85 MPH
 24H  27/1800Z 22.1N  89.9W   65 KT  75 MPH
 36H  28/0600Z 24.2N  91.4W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  28/1800Z 26.8N  91.4W   70 KT  80 MPH
 60H  29/0600Z 30.8N  88.9W   60 KT  70 MPH...INLAND
 72H  29/1800Z 35.0N  83.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 96H  30/1800Z 42.0N  68.0W   35 KT  40 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
120H  31/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 20:49:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/262049.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/262049.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Wind Speed Probabilities Number 10</title>
<description>Issued at 0300 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT3 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
HURRICANE ZETA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  10                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020               
0300 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020                                            
                                                                    
AT 0300Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ZETA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 20.2
NORTH...LONGITUDE 87.1 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 70 KTS
...80 MPH...130 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        00Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       00Z TUE 12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 00Z FRI 00Z SAT 00Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NWS EARLE NJ   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)   X(20)
CAPE HENLOPEN  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)   X(23)   X(23)
OCEAN CITY MD  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
OCEAN CITY MD  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)   X(23)   X(23)
PAX RIVER NAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   X(24)   X(24)
WALLOPS CDA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  27(27)   X(27)   X(27)
RICHMOND VA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   X(24)   X(24)
DANVILLE VA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  24(24)   X(24)   X(24)
NORFOLK NAS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)   X(23)   X(23)
NORFOLK VA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   X(21)   X(21)
OCEANA NAS VA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   X(18)   X(18)
ELIZABETH CTY  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)   X(23)   X(23)
GREENSBORO NC  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)   X(22)   X(22)
RALEIGH NC     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)   X(20)
ROCKY MT NC    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
CHARLESTON SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BEAUFORT MCAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  18(18)   X(18)   X(18)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   7(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   4(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  11(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)  28(35)   X(35)   X(35)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)   X(20)   X(20)
COLUMBUS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  31(34)   X(34)   X(34)
MONTGOMERY AL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  35(44)   X(44)   X(44)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)
WHITING FLD FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  33(45)   X(45)   X(45)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  11(12)   X(12)   X(12)
PENSACOLA FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  22(24)  10(34)   X(34)   X(34)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)  31(53)   X(53)   X(53)
MOBILE AL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  14(17)   X(17)   X(17)
MOBILE AL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  32(33)  21(54)   X(54)   X(54)
GULFPORT MS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)  10(20)   X(20)   X(20)
GULFPORT MS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  34(35)  15(50)   X(50)   X(50)
STENNIS MS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   6(19)   X(19)   X(19)
STENNIS MS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  52(54)  11(65)   X(65)   X(65)
BURAS LA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)   5(28)   X(28)   X(28)
BURAS LA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   2( 2)  15(17)  46(63)   4(67)   X(67)   X(67)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  22(23)   2(25)   X(25)   X(25)
GFMX 280N 890W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
JACKSON MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  34(36)  10(46)   X(46)   X(46)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   4(19)   X(19)   X(19)
NEW ORLEANS LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   3( 3)  29(32)  47(79)   X(79)   X(79)   X(79)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X   X( X)   4( 4)  43(47)   1(48)   X(48)   X(48)
GFMX 280N 910W 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)   4(21)   X(21)   X(21)
BATON ROUGE LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
BATON ROUGE LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   X( X)   3( 3)  26(29)   4(33)   X(33)   X(33)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)
MORGAN CITY LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   2(15)   X(15)   X(15)
NEW IBERIA LA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   1( 1)  14(15)   9(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
GFMX 280N 930W 50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   4( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MERIDA MX      34 46  12(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)
MERIDA MX      50  4   5( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
COZUMEL MX     34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
COZUMEL MX     50 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
COZUMEL MX     64 92   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)   X(92)
 
BELIZE CITY    34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PENSACOLA NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)  23(23)  26(49)   X(49)   X(49)
PENSACOLA NAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  11(13)   X(13)   X(13)
PENSACOLA NAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
KEESLER AB     34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  40(42)  20(62)   X(62)   X(62)
KEESLER AB     50  X   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)  12(24)   X(24)   X(24)
KEESLER AB     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER BLAKE                                                    
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 02:46:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Mon, 26 Oct 2020 23:55:44 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:25:39 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 23:55:44 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL2820_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:14:04 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:14:04 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:49:20 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:49:20 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>09</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Mon, 26 Oct 2020 20:51:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 20:51:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/211404.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  415 PM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:15:42 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for New Orleans / Baton Rouge, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  448 PM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:48:45 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Mobile, AL / Pensacola, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  455 PM CDT Mon Oct 26 2020</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2020 21:56:03 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
