<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 18:12:18 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 271723<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Tue Oct 27 2020<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Zeta, located just offshore of the northwestern <br/>
Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin/Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:23:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202010271723</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Zeta (AT3/AL282020)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al282020-202010271747</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/271747.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ZETA MOVING OVER THE SOUTHERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...EXPECTED TO REGAIN HURRICANE STRENGTH LATER TODAY...
 As of 1:00 PM CDT Tue Oct 27
 the center of Zeta was located near 22.1, -90.1
 with movement NW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 985 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>22.1, -90.1</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Tropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Zeta</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL282020</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>1:00 PM CDT Tue Oct 27</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>985 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ZETA MOVING OVER THE SOUTHERN GULF OF MEXICO... ...EXPECTED TO REGAIN HURRICANE STRENGTH LATER TODAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Public Advisory Number 12A</title>
<description>Issued at 100 PM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT33 KNHC 271747
TCPAT3
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Zeta Intermediate Advisory Number 12A
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
100 PM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020
 
...ZETA MOVING OVER THE SOUTHERN GULF OF MEXICO...
...EXPECTED TO REGAIN HURRICANE STRENGTH LATER TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 100 PM CDT...1800 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...22.1N 90.1W
ABOUT 485 MI...785 KM S OF THE MOUTH OF THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 305 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...985 MB...29.09 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The government of Mexico has discontinued all Tropical Storm
Warnings for the Yucatan Peninsula.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Intracoastal City Louisiana to Navarre Florida
* Lake Borgne, Lake Pontchartrain, Vermilion Bay, Pensacola Bay, and
Mobile Bay
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Morgan City Louisiana to the Mississippi/Alabama border
* Lake Pontchartrain, Lake Maurepas, and Metropolitan New Orleans
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Mississippi/Alabama border to Okaloosa/Walton County Line Florida
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* West of Morgan City to Intracoastal City Louisiana
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a
depiction of areas at risk, please see the National Weather
Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at
hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.  Persons
located within these areas should take all necessary actions to
protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions.  Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of
tropical-storm-force winds, conditions that make outside
preparations difficult or dangerous.  Preparations to protect life
and property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 100 PM CDT (1800 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Zeta was
located near latitude 22.1 North, longitude 90.1 West.  Zeta is
moving toward the northwest near 14 mph (22 km/h), and this general
motion is forecast to continue today.  Zeta should turn toward the
north tonight, and a faster northward to north-northeastward motion
is expected on Wednesday.  On the forecast track, the center of Zeta
will move over the southern Gulf of Mexico today and over the
central Gulf of Mexico tonight.  Zeta is forecast to approach the
northern Gulf Coast on Wednesday, make landfall within the hurricane
warning area late Wednesday or Wednesday night, and move inland
across the southeastern United States early Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Zeta is forecast to re-strengthen while it moves over the
southern Gulf of Mexico, and become a hurricane again later today.
Zeta is forecast to be at or near hurricane strength when it reaches
the northern Gulf Coast late Wednesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.
 
The estimated minimum central pressure is 985 mb (29.09 inches).
 
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Zeta can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43 KNHC, and
on the web at www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
STORM SURGE:  Along the northern Gulf Coast, the combination of a
dangerous storm surge and the tide will cause normally dry areas
near the coast to be flooded by rising waters moving inland from the
shoreline.  The water could reach the following heights above ground
somewhere in the indicated areas if the peak surge occurs at the
time of high tide...
 
Mouth of the Pearl River to Dauphin Island AL...5-8 ft
Port Fourchon LA to the Mouth of the Pearl River including Lake
Borgne...4-6 ft
Dauphin Island AL to AL/FL border including Mobile Bay...3-5 ft
Intracoastal City LA to Port Fourchon LA including Vermilion
Bay...2-4 ft
AL/FL border to Navarre FL including Pensacola Bay...2-4 ft
Lake Pontchartrain...2-4 ft
Navarre FL to Yankeetown FL including Choctawhatchee Bay and Saint
Andrew Bay...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle,
and can vary greatly over short distances.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
Water levels along the coast of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico
will gradually subside today as Zeta moves away from the area.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane
Warning area on the northern Gulf Coast late Wednesday, with
tropical storm conditions beginning Wednesday afternoon. Tropical
storm conditions are expected within the Tropical Storm Warning
area on the northern Gulf coast by late Wednesday, and tropical
storm conditions are possible within the Tropical Storm Watch area
late Wednesday.
 
Damaging winds, especially in gusts, will spread well inland across
portions of southeast Mississippi and southern Alabama Wednesday
night.
 
RAINFALL:  Rainfall totals of 4 to 8 inches with local amounts of 12
inches are possible through today across the Yucatan Peninsula of
Mexico and the Cayman Islands. An additional 1 to 3 inches of rain
will be possible across western Cuba through Tuesday.
 
An initial area of heavy rains will begin to impact the central Gulf
Coast tonight, with the core of heavy rains spreading north into the
Ohio Valley and Mid-Atlantic through Thursday, near and in advance
of Zeta. Rainfall totals of 2 to 4 inches with isolated amounts of 6
inches are expected across these areas, resulting in flash, urban,
small stream, and minor river flooding.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are possible Wednesday and Wednesday
night over southeastern Mississippi, southern Alabama, and the
western Panhandle of Florida.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:47:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/271747.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/271747.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Forecast Advisory Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 271445
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM ZETA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  12
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020
1500 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
NONE.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* INTRACOASTAL CITY LOUISIANA TO NAVARRE FLORIDA
* LAKE BORGNE...LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...VERMILION BAY...PENSACOLA
BAY...AND
MOBILE BAY
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MORGAN CITY LOUISIANA TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER
* LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...LAKE MAUREPAS...AND METROPOLITAN NEW ORLEANS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* PUNTA ALLEN TO PROGRESO MEXICO
* COZUMEL
* MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER TO OKALOOSA/WALTON COUNTY LINE FLORIDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* WEST OF MORGAN CITY TO INTRACOASTAL CITY LOUISIANA
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING 
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE 
COASTLINE...DURING THE NEXT 36 HOURS IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR 
A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER 
SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT 
HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION.  PERSONS 
LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS TO 
PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR 
OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.  PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER 
INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.6N  89.5W AT 27/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 305 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  985 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 70NE  70SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT.......120NE 120SE  60SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE   0SE   0SW  30NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 21.6N  89.5W AT 27/1500Z
AT 27/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.3N  89.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0000Z 23.1N  90.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 25.7N  91.6W
MAX WIND  75 KT...GUSTS  90 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  50SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0000Z 29.3N  89.9W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE   0SW  10NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1200Z 34.2N  85.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0000Z 38.5N  76.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1200Z 41.0N  66.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 60NE 220SE 300SW  60NW.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 31/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 21.6N  89.5W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 27/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 27/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:45:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/271445.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/271445.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

811 
WTNT43 KNHC 271451
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Zeta Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
1000 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020
 
High-resolution GOES-16 visible satellite images indicate that the 
center of Zeta has moved just offshore of the northern coast of 
Yucatan.  Based on Air Force and NOAA aircraft observations a little 
while ago, after the cyclone's interaction with the Yucatan, the 
maximum winds had decreased to near 55 kt.  The cloud pattern of the 
storm is well organized, with a small Central Dense Overcast and 
numerous banding features.  Given this, Zeta is likely to 
restrengthen as it moves over the warm waters of the southern Gulf 
of Mexico and in a low-shear environment today through tomorrow 
morning.  When the cyclone nears the northern Gulf Coast in 30-36 
hours, decreasing oceanic heat content and possibly stronger shear 
will likely halt the intensification process.  The official 
intensity forecast shows slight weakening near landfall, but Zeta is 
likely to be at or near hurricane strength when it crosses the 
coastline.  The NHC intensity forecast is close to the model 
consensus and a blend of the LGEM and Decay-SHIPS guidance.
 
The storm continues its generally northwestward motion, or at around 
305/12 kt.  Zeta will move northwestward to northward around the 
southwestern and western periphery of a mid-level high pressure area 
centered east of Florida for the next 24 hours or so.  Then, a 
strong 500-mb shortwave trough approaching from the west should 
cause Zeta to accelerate north-northeastward to northeastward by 
late Wednesday and Thursday.  This will bring Zeta across the 
north-central Gulf coast late Wednesday and over the southeastern 
United States on Thursday.  Aside from some speed differences, the 
track models are in good agreement and have shown good run-to-run 
consistency.  The official track forecast is about the same as the 
previous one and close to the model consensus.

Given Zeta's acceleration near landfall, strong winds are likely 
to spread well inland along the northern Gulf coast Wednesday 
night. 

KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. A life-threatening storm surge is expected along portions of the 
northern Gulf Coast by late Wednesday, with the highest inundation 
occurring somewhere between the Mouth of the Pearl River and Dauphin 
Island, Alabama.  Residents in the Storm Surge Warning area should 
follow any advice given by local officials.

2. Hurricane conditions are expected by late Wednesday within 
portions of the Hurricane Warning area between Morgan City, 
Louisiana, and the Mississippi/Alabama border.  Damaging winds, 
especially in gusts, will spread well inland across portions of 
southeast Mississippi and southern Alabama Wednesday night due to 
Zetas fast forward speed. 

3. Between tonight and Thursday, heavy rainfall is expected from 
portions of the central U.S. Gulf Coast into the Ohio Valley and 
Mid-Atlantic States near and in advance of Zeta.  This rainfall 
will lead to flash, urban, small stream, and minor river flooding.

4. Tropical storm conditions will continue in portions of the 
northern Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico during the next few hours. 
Heavy rainfall is expected across the Yucatan Peninsula, the Cayman 
Islands, and western Cuba today, which will lead to flash flooding 
in urban areas.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  27/1500Z 21.6N  89.5W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  28/0000Z 23.1N  90.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  28/1200Z 25.7N  91.6W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  29/0000Z 29.3N  89.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  29/1200Z 34.2N  85.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  30/0000Z 38.5N  76.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  30/1200Z 41.0N  66.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  31/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:51:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/271451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/271451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Wind Speed Probabilities Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT13 KNHC 271448
PWSAT3
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ZETA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  12             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020               
1500 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ZETA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
21.6 NORTH...LONGITUDE 89.5 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z TUE 00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z WED 12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
HYANNIS MA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
PROVIDENCE RI  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BRIDGEPORT CT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEW HAVEN CT   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NEW LONDON CT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ISLIP NY       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
NYC CNTRL PARK 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
NEWARK NJ      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NWS EARLE NJ   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ALLENTOWN PA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   X(14)   X(14)
DOVER DE       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  12(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   X(21)   X(21)
CAPE HENLOPEN  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  22(22)   X(22)   X(22)
OCEAN CITY MD  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
OCEAN CITY MD  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  19(19)   X(19)   X(19)
PAX RIVER NAS  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  21(21)   X(21)   X(21)
WALLOPS CDA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
WALLOPS CDA    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)   X(20)
RICHMOND VA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   X(17)   X(17)
NORFOLK NAS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
NORFOLK NAS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  17(17)   X(17)   X(17)
NORFOLK VA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
NORFOLK VA     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
OCEANA NAS VA  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
OCEANA NAS VA  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)   X(13)
ELIZABETH CTY  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
RALEIGH NC     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   X(14)   X(14)
ROCKY MT NC    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HATTERAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  13(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
CHERRY PT NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
NEW RIVER NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MOREHEAD CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
SURF CITY NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WILMINGTON NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BALD HEAD ISL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FLORENCE SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
LITTLE RIVER   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MYRTLE BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GEORGETOWN SC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   2(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   8(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   7( 7)  10(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   8( 8)   6(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)  11(11)  15(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)  11(11)  35(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  24(25)   1(26)   X(26)   X(26)
COLUMBUS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   2( 2)  14(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  36(40)   X(40)   X(40)   X(40)
MONTGOMERY AL  50  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)  14(14)  43(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
WHITING FLD FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)  17(17)  44(61)   X(61)   X(61)   X(61)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
PENSACOLA FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   2( 2)  34(36)  11(47)   X(47)   X(47)   X(47)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)  31(31)  34(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
MOBILE AL      50  X   X( X)   6( 6)  22(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
MOBILE AL      64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   1( 1)  46(47)  20(67)   X(67)   X(67)   X(67)
GULFPORT MS    50  X   X( X)  17(17)  12(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
GULFPORT MS    64  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   1( 1)  49(50)  13(63)   X(63)   X(63)   X(63)
STENNIS MS     50  X   X( X)  20(20)   7(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
STENNIS MS     64  X   X( X)   4( 4)   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   4( 4)  73(77)   5(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)
BURAS LA       50  X   X( X)  43(43)   6(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
BURAS LA       64  X   X( X)   9( 9)   2(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X  19(19)  60(79)   1(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   1( 1)  36(37)   1(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
GFMX 280N 890W 64  X   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
JACKSON MS     34  X   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X   3( 3)  47(50)   5(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50  X   X( X)  22(22)   4(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
NEW ORLEANS LA 64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  2  33(35)  52(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X   4( 4)  57(61)   X(61)   X(61)   X(61)   X(61)
GFMX 280N 910W 64  X   X( X)  24(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)   X(24)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   2( 2)  18(20)   3(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
BATON ROUGE LA 50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   4( 4)  31(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  X   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
MORGAN CITY LA 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   2( 2)   9(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   3( 3)  11(14)   2(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
NEW IBERIA LA  50  X   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  1  13(14)   8(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   5( 5)   3( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  X   5( 5)   2( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  1   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MERIDA MX      34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
MERIDA MX      50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
COZUMEL MX     34  3   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PENSACOLA NAS  34  X   X( X)  33(33)  32(65)   X(65)   X(65)   X(65)
PENSACOLA NAS  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)  17(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
PENSACOLA NAS  64  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
KEESLER AB     34  X   1( 1)  57(58)  17(75)   X(75)   X(75)   X(75)
KEESLER AB     50  X   X( X)  20(20)  19(39)   X(39)   X(39)   X(39)
KEESLER AB     64  X   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:48:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/271448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/271448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:45:10 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:25:22 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:45:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL2820_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:12:01 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:12:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:04:43 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>12</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:50:50 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:50:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Birmingham, AL</title>
<description>Issued at  1020 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:20:19 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBMX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBMX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  1027 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jackson, MS</title>
<description>Issued at  1036 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Mobile, AL / Pensacola, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1114 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:14:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for New Orleans / Baton Rouge, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  1204 PM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
