<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 20:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 271723<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
200 PM EDT Tue Oct 27 2020<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Tropical <br/>
Storm Zeta, located just offshore of the northwestern <br/>
Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Papin/Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:23:12 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202010271723</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Tropical Storm Zeta (AT3/AL282020)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al282020-202010272040</guid>
 <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 20:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...ZETA EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND STORM SURGE TO A PORTION OF THE NORTHERN GULF COAST TOMORROW...
 As of 4:00 PM CDT Tue Oct 27
 the center of Zeta was located near 22.7, -90.3
 with movement NW at 14 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 984 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 65 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>22.7, -90.3</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>TROPICAL STORM</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Zeta</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL282020</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>4:00 PM CDT Tue Oct 27</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NW at 14 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>984 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>65 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...ZETA EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND STORM SURGE TO A PORTION OF THE NORTHERN GULF COAST TOMORROW...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Public Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 400 PM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCPAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Tropical Storm Zeta Advisory Number  13
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
400 PM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020
 
...ZETA EXPECTED TO BRING HURRICANE CONDITIONS AND STORM SURGE TO A
PORTION OF THE NORTHERN GULF COAST TOMORROW...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 400 PM CDT...2100 UTC...INFORMATION
----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...22.7N 90.3W
ABOUT 450 MI...720 KM S OF THE MOUTH OF THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...65 MPH...100 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NW OR 310 DEGREES AT 14 MPH...22 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...984 MB...29.06 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Storm Surge Warning from Intracoastal City, Louisiana, to the
Mouth of the Atchafalaya River has been discontinued.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Mouth of the Atchafalaya River to Navarre Florida
* Lake Borgne, Lake Pontchartrain, Pensacola Bay and Mobile Bay
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Morgan City Louisiana to the Mississippi/Alabama border
* Lake Pontchartrain, Lake Maurepas, and Metropolitan New Orleans
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Mississippi/Alabama border to Okaloosa/Walton County Line Florida
 
A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* West of Morgan City to Intracoastal City Louisiana
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline,
during the next 36 hours in the indicated locations. For a depiction
of areas at risk, please see the National Weather Service Storm
Surge Watch/Warning Graphic, available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a
life-threatening situation.  Persons located within these areas
should take all necessary actions to protect life and property from
rising water and the potential for other dangerous conditions.
Promptly follow evacuation and other instructions from local
officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  A warning is typically issued
36 hours before the anticipated first occurrence of tropical-storm-
force winds, conditions that make outside preparations difficult or
dangerous.  Preparations to protect life and property should be
rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area within 36 hours.
 
A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, generally within 48 hours.
 
For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 400 PM CDT (2100 UTC), the center of Tropical Storm Zeta was
located near latitude 22.7 North, longitude 90.3 West.  Zeta is
moving toward the northwest near 14 mph (22 km/h).  A turn toward
the north is expected tonight, and a faster northward to north-
northeastward motion is expected on Wednesday.  On the forecast
track, the center of Zeta will move over the central Gulf of Mexico
tonight.  Zeta is forecast to approach the northern Gulf Coast on
Wednesday, make landfall within the hurricane warning area late
Wednesday or Wednesday night, and move across the southeastern and
eastern United States on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 65 mph (100 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Zeta is forecast to become a hurricane again tonight and is
forecast to be at or near hurricane strength when it reaches the
northern Gulf Coast late Wednesday.
 
Tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 140 miles (220 km)
from the center.

The estimated minimum central pressure is 984 mb (29.06 inches).
 

HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Zeta can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43 KNHC, and
on the web at www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
STORM SURGE:  Along the northern Gulf Coast, the combination of a
dangerous storm surge and the tide will cause normally dry areas
near the coast to be flooded by rising waters moving inland from the
shoreline.  The water could reach the following heights above ground
somewhere in the indicated areas if the peak surge occurs at the
time of high tide...
 
Mouth of the Pearl River to Dauphin Island AL...5-8 ft
Port Fourchon LA to the Mouth of the Pearl River including Lake
Borgne...4-6 ft
Dauphin Island AL to AL/FL border including Mobile Bay...3-5 ft
Mouth of the Atchafalaya River to Port Fourchon LA...2-4 ft
AL/FL border to Navarre FL including Pensacola Bay...2-4 ft
Lake Pontchartrain...2-4 ft
Intracoastal City LA to the Mouth of the Atchafalaya River
including Vermilion Bay...1-3 ft
Navarre FL to Yankeetown FL including Choctawhatchee Bay and Saint
Andrew Bay...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle,
and can vary greatly over short distances.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane
Warning area on the northern Gulf Coast late Wednesday, with
tropical storm conditions beginning Wednesday afternoon.  Tropical
storm conditions are expected within the Tropical Storm Warning
area on the northern Gulf Coast by late Wednesday, and tropical
storm conditions are possible within the Tropical Storm Watch area
late Wednesday.
 
Damaging winds, especially in gusts, will spread well inland across
portions of southeast Mississippi and southern Alabama Wednesday
night.
 
RAINFALL:  An initial area of heavy rains will begin to impact the
central Gulf Coast tonight, with the core of heavy rains spreading
north into the Ohio Valley and Mid-Atlantic through Thursday, near
and in advance of Zeta.  Rainfall totals of 2 to 4 inches with
isolated amounts of 6 inches are expected across these areas,
resulting in flash, urban, small stream, and minor river flooding.
 
Zeta will produce an additional 1 to 3 inches of rain across
portions of western Cuba and the northern Yucatan Peninsula through
tonight.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are expected Wednesday and Wednesday 
night over southeastern Mississippi, southern Alabama, and the 
western Panhandle of Florida.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 700 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 1000 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 20:40:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Forecast Advisory Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 272040
TCMAT3
 
TROPICAL STORM ZETA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  13
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020
2100 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE STORM SURGE WARNING FROM INTRACOASTAL CITY LOUISIANA TO THE
MOUTH OF THE ATCHAFALAYA RIVER HAS BEEN DISCONTINUED.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE ATCHAFALAYA RIVER TO NAVARRE FLORIDA
* LAKE BORGNE...LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...PENSACOLA BAY AND MOBILE BAY
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MORGAN CITY LOUISIANA TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER
* LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...LAKE MAUREPAS...AND METROPOLITAN NEW ORLEANS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER TO OKALOOSA/WALTON COUNTY LINE FLORIDA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* WEST OF MORGAN CITY TO INTRACOASTAL CITY LOUISIANA
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING 
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE... 
DURING THE NEXT 36 HOURS IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION 
OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM 
SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC...AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS 
A LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION.  PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS 
SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM 
RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS. 
PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL 
OFFICIALS.
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED 
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 36 
HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM- 
FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR 
DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE 
RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.7N  90.3W AT 27/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTHWEST OR 310 DEGREES AT  12 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  984 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  55 KT WITH GUSTS TO  65 KT.
50 KT....... 70NE  70SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT.......120NE 120SE  60SW  70NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE  60SE  30SW  60NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.7N  90.3W AT 27/2100Z
AT 27/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 22.2N  90.0W
 
FORECAST VALID 28/0600Z 24.5N  91.3W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  20SW  40NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  60SW  70NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 28/1800Z 27.9N  91.0W
MAX WIND  70 KT...GUSTS  85 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  20SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  20SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 120SE  60SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0600Z 32.4N  87.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE  50SW  50NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1800Z 37.2N  81.3W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0600Z 40.0N  70.5W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 200SE 200SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 22.7N  90.3W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 28/0000Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 28/0300Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 20:40:21 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/272040.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/272040.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Forecast Discussion Number 12</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

811 
WTNT43 KNHC 271451
TCDAT3
 
Tropical Storm Zeta Discussion Number  12
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
1000 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020
 
High-resolution GOES-16 visible satellite images indicate that the 
center of Zeta has moved just offshore of the northern coast of 
Yucatan.  Based on Air Force and NOAA aircraft observations a little 
while ago, after the cyclone's interaction with the Yucatan, the 
maximum winds had decreased to near 55 kt.  The cloud pattern of the 
storm is well organized, with a small Central Dense Overcast and 
numerous banding features.  Given this, Zeta is likely to 
restrengthen as it moves over the warm waters of the southern Gulf 
of Mexico and in a low-shear environment today through tomorrow 
morning.  When the cyclone nears the northern Gulf Coast in 30-36 
hours, decreasing oceanic heat content and possibly stronger shear 
will likely halt the intensification process.  The official 
intensity forecast shows slight weakening near landfall, but Zeta is 
likely to be at or near hurricane strength when it crosses the 
coastline.  The NHC intensity forecast is close to the model 
consensus and a blend of the LGEM and Decay-SHIPS guidance.
 
The storm continues its generally northwestward motion, or at around 
305/12 kt.  Zeta will move northwestward to northward around the 
southwestern and western periphery of a mid-level high pressure area 
centered east of Florida for the next 24 hours or so.  Then, a 
strong 500-mb shortwave trough approaching from the west should 
cause Zeta to accelerate north-northeastward to northeastward by 
late Wednesday and Thursday.  This will bring Zeta across the 
north-central Gulf coast late Wednesday and over the southeastern 
United States on Thursday.  Aside from some speed differences, the 
track models are in good agreement and have shown good run-to-run 
consistency.  The official track forecast is about the same as the 
previous one and close to the model consensus.

Given Zeta's acceleration near landfall, strong winds are likely 
to spread well inland along the northern Gulf coast Wednesday 
night. 

KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. A life-threatening storm surge is expected along portions of the 
northern Gulf Coast by late Wednesday, with the highest inundation 
occurring somewhere between the Mouth of the Pearl River and Dauphin 
Island, Alabama.  Residents in the Storm Surge Warning area should 
follow any advice given by local officials.

2. Hurricane conditions are expected by late Wednesday within 
portions of the Hurricane Warning area between Morgan City, 
Louisiana, and the Mississippi/Alabama border.  Damaging winds, 
especially in gusts, will spread well inland across portions of 
southeast Mississippi and southern Alabama Wednesday night due to 
Zetas fast forward speed. 

3. Between tonight and Thursday, heavy rainfall is expected from 
portions of the central U.S. Gulf Coast into the Ohio Valley and 
Mid-Atlantic States near and in advance of Zeta.  This rainfall 
will lead to flash, urban, small stream, and minor river flooding.

4. Tropical storm conditions will continue in portions of the 
northern Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico during the next few hours. 
Heavy rainfall is expected across the Yucatan Peninsula, the Cayman 
Islands, and western Cuba today, which will lead to flash flooding 
in urban areas.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  27/1500Z 21.6N  89.5W   55 KT  65 MPH
 12H  28/0000Z 23.1N  90.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 24H  28/1200Z 25.7N  91.6W   75 KT  85 MPH
 36H  29/0000Z 29.3N  89.9W   70 KT  80 MPH
 48H  29/1200Z 34.2N  85.2W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 60H  30/0000Z 38.5N  76.5W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
 72H  30/1200Z 41.0N  66.0W   45 KT  50 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 96H  31/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:51:06 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/271451.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/271451.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Wind Speed Probabilities Number 13</title>
<description>Issued at 2100 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT3 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
TROPICAL STORM ZETA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  13             
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020               
2100 UTC TUE OCT 27 2020                                            
                                                                    
AT 2100Z THE CENTER OF TROPICAL STORM ZETA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE
22.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 90.3 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR  
55 KTS...65 MPH...100 KM/H.                                         
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        18Z TUE AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       18Z TUE 06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             06Z WED 18Z WED 06Z THU 18Z THU 18Z FRI 18Z SAT 18Z SUN
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MONTAUK POINT  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NYC JFK AIRPRT 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TRENTON NJ     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
NWS EARLE NJ   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PHILADELPHIA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BALTIMORE MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  16(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  14(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  15(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   7(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   4( 4)  26(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)
ATLANTA GA     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
SAVANNAH GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   9( 9)   1(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   1( 1)  12(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   1( 1)  11(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   2( 2)  17(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)   X(19)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   3( 3)  32(35)   1(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)  13(13)  15(28)   X(28)   X(28)   X(28)
COLUMBUS GA    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)  20(20)  10(30)   X(30)   X(30)   X(30)
BIRMINGHAM AL  50  X   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)  37(37)   9(46)   X(46)   X(46)   X(46)
MONTGOMERY AL  50  X   X( X)   7( 7)   4(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   3( 3)  45(48)   1(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)  10(10)   1(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   4( 4)  47(51)   1(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)  11(11)   1(12)   X(12)   X(12)   X(12)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X  14(14)  24(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)   X(38)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   5( 5)  68(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)   X(73)
MOBILE AL      50  X   X( X)  36(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)   X(36)
MOBILE AL      64  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   7( 7)  69(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)   X(76)
GULFPORT MS    50  X   X( X)  45(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)   X(45)
GULFPORT MS    64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X  10(10)  61(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)   X(71)
STENNIS MS     50  X   1( 1)  36(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)   X(37)
STENNIS MS     64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
BURAS LA       34  X  33(33)  53(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)   X(86)
BURAS LA       50  X   5( 5)  50(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)
BURAS LA       64  X   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  6  59(65)  12(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X  15(15)  12(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
GFMX 280N 890W 64  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
JACKSON MS     34  X   1( 1)   8( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X  19(19)  43(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50  X   3( 3)  29(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)   X(32)
NEW ORLEANS LA 64  X   X( X)   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  7  85(92)   1(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)   X(93)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X  79(79)   3(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)   X(82)
GFMX 280N 910W 64  X  28(28)   3(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)   X(31)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   8( 8)  15(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
BATON ROUGE LA 50  X   1( 1)   4( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X  24(24)  19(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)   X(43)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  X   4( 4)  11(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
MORGAN CITY LA 64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   5( 5)   6(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   8( 8)   8(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  4  25(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)   X(29)
GFMX 280N 930W 50  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   7( 7)   2( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
GFMX 280N 950W 34  2   4( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MATAGORDA TX   34  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 270N 960W 34  2   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
GFMX 250N 960W 34  3   2( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
MERIDA MX      34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
 
PENSACOLA NAS  34  X   9( 9)  46(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)   X(55)
PENSACOLA NAS  50  X   X( X)  12(12)   1(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
PENSACOLA NAS  64  X   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
KEESLER AB     34  X  20(20)  60(80)   1(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
KEESLER AB     50  X   1( 1)  47(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)   X(48)
KEESLER AB     64  X   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 20:40:24 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:45:10 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:25:22 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:45:10 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL2820_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:12:01 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:12:01 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:04:43 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:04:43 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>12</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Tropical Storm Zeta Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Tropical Storm Zeta Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:50:50 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 14:50:50 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/151201.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  1027 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:28:11 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jackson, MS</title>
<description>Issued at  1036 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 15:36:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Mobile, AL / Pensacola, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  1114 AM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 16:14:25 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for New Orleans / Baton Rouge, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  1204 PM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:04:53 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Birmingham, AL</title>
<description>Issued at  326 PM CDT Tue Oct 27 2020</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 20:27:08 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBMX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBMX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
