<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 14:48:52 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 281131<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
800 AM EDT Wed Oct 28 2020<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on Hurricane <br/>
Zeta, located over the central Gulf of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Berg<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 11:31:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;202010281131</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Hurricane Zeta (AT3/AL282020)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al282020-202010281448</guid>
 <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 14:48:36 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...CONDITIONS DETERIORATING ALONG PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN GULF COAST... ...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND DAMAGING WINDS LIKELY IN THE WARNING AREAS LATER TODAY...
 As of 10:00 AM CDT Wed Oct 28
 the center of Zeta was located near 26.9, -91.7
 with movement N at 18 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 976 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 90 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>26.9, -91.7</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Hurricane</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Zeta</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT3</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL282020</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM CDT Wed Oct 28</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>N at 18 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>976 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>90 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...CONDITIONS DETERIORATING ALONG PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN GULF COAST... ...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND DAMAGING WINDS LIKELY IN THE WARNING AREAS LATER TODAY...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Public Advisory Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCPAT3 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
BULLETIN
Hurricane Zeta Advisory Number  16
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
1000 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020
 
...CONDITIONS DETERIORATING ALONG PORTIONS OF THE NORTHERN GULF
COAST...
...LIFE-THREATENING STORM SURGE AND DAMAGING WINDS LIKELY IN THE
WARNING AREAS LATER TODAY...
 
 
SUMMARY OF 1000 AM CDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...26.9N 91.7W
ABOUT 220 MI...355 KM SW OF THE MOUTH OF THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER
ABOUT 235 MI...380 KM SSW OF NEW ORLEANS LOUISIANA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...90 MPH...150 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...N OR 10 DEGREES AT 18 MPH...30 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...976 MB...28.82 INCHES
 
 
WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:
 
The Tropical Storm Watch west of Morgan City to Intracoastal City,
Louisiana is discontinued.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:
 
A Storm Surge Warning is in effect for...
* Mouth of the Atchafalaya River to Navarre Florida
* Lake Borgne, Lake Pontchartrain, Pensacola Bay and Mobile Bay
 
A Hurricane Warning is in effect for...
* Morgan City Louisiana to the Mississippi/Alabama border
* Lake Pontchartrain, Lake Maurepas, and Metropolitan New Orleans
 
A Tropical Storm Warning is in effect for...
* Mississippi/Alabama border to Walton/Bay County Line Florida
 
A Storm Surge Warning means there is a danger of life-threatening
inundation, from rising water moving inland from the coastline in
the indicated locations. For a depiction of areas at risk, please
see the National Weather Service Storm Surge Watch/Warning Graphic,
available at hurricanes.gov.  This is a life-threatening situation.
Persons located within these areas should take all necessary actions
to protect life and property from rising water and the potential for
other dangerous conditions. Promptly follow evacuation and other
instructions from local officials.
 
A Hurricane Warning means that hurricane conditions are expected
somewhere within the warning area.  Preparations to protect life and
property should be rushed to completion.
 
A Tropical Storm Warning means that tropical storm conditions are
expected somewhere within the warning area.
 
For storm information specific to your area, including possible
inland watches and warnings, please monitor products issued by your
local National Weather Service forecast office.
 
 
DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM CDT (1500 UTC), the center of Hurricane Zeta was located
near latitude 26.9 North, longitude 91.7 West. Zeta is moving toward
the north near 18 mph (30 km/h).  A faster northward to north-
northeastward motion is expected through tonight followed by an even
faster northeastward motion on Thursday and an east-northeastward
motion early Friday.  On the forecast track, the center of Zeta will
make landfall in southeastern Louisiana this afternoon.  Zeta will
then move close to the Mississippi coast this evening, and move
across the southeastern and eastern United States on Thursday.
 
Maximum sustained winds are near 90 mph (150 km/h) with higher
gusts.  Some additional strengthening is possible during the
next few hours, and Zeta is expected to reach the northern Gulf
Coast as a hurricane before weakening over the southeastern United
States on Thursday.
 
Hurricane-force winds extend outward up to 35 miles (55 km) from the
center and tropical-storm-force winds extend outward up to 150 miles
(240 km).
 
The minimum central pressure estimated from Air Force Hurricane
Hunter aircraft observations is 976 mb (28.82 inches).
  
 
HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
Key messages for Zeta can be found in the Tropical Cyclone
Discussion under AWIPS header MIATCDAT3, WMO header WTNT43 KNHC, and
on the web at www.hurricanes.gov/text/MIATCDAT3.shtml.
 
STORM SURGE:  Along the northern Gulf Coast, the combination of a
dangerous storm surge and the tide will cause normally dry areas
near the coast to be flooded by rising waters moving inland from the
shoreline.  The water could reach the following heights above ground
somewhere in the indicated areas if the peak surge occurs at the
time of high tide...
 
Mouth of the Pearl River to Dauphin Island AL...6-9 ft
Port Fourchon LA to the Mouth of the Mississippi River...5-8 ft
Mouth of the Mississippi River to the Mouth of the Pearl River
including Lake Borgne...5-7 ft
Mouth of the Atchafalaya River to Port Fourchon LA...4-6 ft
Mobile Bay...4-6 ft
Dauphin Island AL to AL/FL border...3-5 ft
Lake Pontchartrain...3-5 ft
AL/FL border to Navarre FL including Pensacola Bay...2-4 ft
Intracoastal City LA to the Mouth of the Atchafalaya River including
Vermilion Bay...1-3 ft
Navarre FL to Yankeetown FL including Choctawhatchee Bay and Saint
Andrew Bay...1-3 ft
 
The deepest water will occur along the immediate coast near and to
the right of the landfall location, where the surge will be
accompanied by large and dangerous waves.  Surge-related flooding
depends on the relative timing of the surge and the tidal cycle,
and can vary greatly over short distances.  For information
specific to your area, please see products issued by your local
National Weather Service forecast office.
 
WIND:  Hurricane conditions are expected within the Hurricane
Warning area on the northern Gulf Coast this afternoon, with
tropical storm conditions beginning later this morning. Tropical
storm conditions are expected within the Tropical Storm Warning
area on the northern Gulf Coast by late today.
 
Damaging winds, especially in gusts, will spread well inland across
portions of southeastern Mississippi, Alabama, and northern Georgia
this evening through early Thursday morning, and into the Carolinas
and southeastern Virginia on Thursday.  Wind gusts could be
especially severe across the southern Appalachian Mountains on
Thursday.
 
RAINFALL:  Areas of heavy rainfall, both in advance of and along the
track of Zeta, will impact areas from the central Gulf Coast to
the Mid-Mississippi and Ohio Valleys, and eastward into the
southern to central Appalachians and Mid-Atlantic today through
Thursday.  Rainfall totals of 2 to 4 inches with isolated amounts
of 6 inches are expected across these areas, resulting in flash,
urban, small stream, and minor river flooding.
 
TORNADOES:  A few tornadoes are expected this afternoon through
tonight over southeastern parts of Louisiana and Mississippi,
southern Alabama, and the western Panhandle of Florida.
 
 
NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.
 
$$
Forecaster Pasch
 
NNNN
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 14:48:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Forecast Advisory Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED OCT 28 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT23 KNHC 281448
TCMAT3
 
HURRICANE ZETA FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  16
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020
1500 UTC WED OCT 28 2020
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH WEST OF MORGAN CITY TO INTRACOASTAL
CITY...LOUISIANA IS DISCONTINUED.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE ATCHAFALAYA RIVER TO NAVARRE FLORIDA
* LAKE BORGNE...LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...PENSACOLA BAY AND MOBILE BAY
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MORGAN CITY LOUISIANA TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER
* LAKE PONTCHARTRAIN...LAKE MAUREPAS...AND METROPOLITAN NEW ORLEANS
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER TO WALTON/BAY COUNTY LINE FLORIDA
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE IN
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING
GRAPHIC...
AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION.
PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY
ACTIONS
TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL
FOR
OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS. PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER
INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND
PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.
 
HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.9N  91.7W AT 28/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR  10 DEGREES AT  16 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  976 MB
EYE DIAMETER  25 NM
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  80 KT WITH GUSTS TO 100 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE  30SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  60SE  20SW  20NW.
34 KT.......120NE 130SE  40SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS..180NE 150SE  90SW 120NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 26.9N  91.7W AT 28/1500Z
AT 28/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 26.0N  91.8W
 
FORECAST VALID 29/0000Z 30.1N  89.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  80 KT...GUSTS 100 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  35SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 60NE  70SE  30SW  30NW.
34 KT...120NE 140SE  50SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 29/1200Z 35.3N  83.9W...INLAND
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
34 KT... 60NE  80SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/0000Z 39.1N  74.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 60NE 140SE 140SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 30/1200Z 41.5N  63.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT... 80NE 210SE 210SW  30NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 31/0000Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 26.9N  91.7W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT33 KNHC/MIATCPAT3...AT 28/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 28/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER PASCH
 
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 14:48:28 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/281448.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT3+shtml/281448.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Forecast Discussion Number 15</title>
<description>Issued at 400 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT43 KNHC 280900
TCDAT3
 
Hurricane Zeta Discussion Number  15
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL282020
400 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020
 
The satellite presentation of Zeta has improved significantly 
overnight with deep convection wrapping around an eye that at times 
as been fairly well defined.  An Air Force Reserve Hurricane Hunter 
aircraft that has just began its reconnaissance mission into Zeta 
has reported a pressure that has fallen to 982 mb and a 25-30 
n-mi-wide eye during it first pass through the center. It is 
somewhat surprising that the plane did not report stronger winds 
during its northeast eyewall pass given the improved satellite 
presentation, and using a blend of the aircraft data and recent 
objective and subjective satellite estimates yields and initial 
intensity of 75 kt.  It is possible the winds have yet to catch up 
to the improved satellite appearance, but since Zeta will moving 
over warm waters and in a light wind shear environment this morning 
some additional strengthening is likely.   Although cooler waters 
and increasing southwesterly upper-level winds over the northern 
Gulf of Mexico are likely to cause the cyclone's intensity to 
level-off or even come down slightly, Zeta is expected to reach the 
northern Gulf coast as significant hurricane by late this afternoon. 
The NHC intensity forecast is at the upper-end of the guidance, a 
little above the latest HWRF prediction. After landfall, Zeta will 
weaken while it moves over the southeastern United States, but the 
cyclone is forecast to become an extratropical gale-force low 
pressure area off the Mid-Atlantic coast Thursday night.  The 
post-tropical cyclone should be absorbed by frontal boundary over 
the western Atlantic on Friday.
 
Zeta has turned north-northwestward and has begun to accelerate as
anticipated.  A vigorous upper-level low moving into west Texas
will cause Zeta to accelerate north-northeastward today, which will
bring the center of the hurricane over southeastern Louisiana by
late this afternoon.  The cyclone is expected to continue to
accelerate ahead of the trough over the southeastern United States
tonight and Thursday. The dynamical model are in very good
agreement and the latest NHC track is a blend of the various global
models. The new track forecast is very close the previous official
forecast.
 
Given Zeta's acceleration near landfall, strong winds are likely
to spread well inland along the northern Gulf coast this evening
and tonight.
 
KEY MESSAGES:
 
1. A life-threatening storm surge is expected along portions of the
northern Gulf Coast by late today, with the highest inundation
occurring somewhere between the Mouth of the Pearl River and Dauphin
Island, Alabama. Residents in the Storm Surge Warning area should
follow any advice given by local officials.
 
2. Hurricane conditions are expected this afternoon within portions 
of the Hurricane Warning area between Morgan City, Louisiana, and 
the Mississippi/Alabama border. Damaging winds, especially in gusts, 
will spread well inland across portions of southeast Mississippi and 
southern and central Alabama tonight due to Zeta's fast forward 
speed.

3. Through Thursday, heavy rainfall is expected from portions of the 
central U.S. Gulf Coast into the Tennessee Valley, Ohio Valley, 
Southern to Central Appalachians, and Mid-Atlantic States near and 
in advance of Zeta. This rainfall will lead to flash, urban, small 
stream, and minor river flooding.
 
FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS
 
INIT  28/0900Z 25.1N  91.8W   75 KT  85 MPH
 12H  28/1800Z 27.9N  91.1W   85 KT 100 MPH
 24H  29/0600Z 32.8N  87.5W   50 KT  60 MPH...INLAND
 36H  29/1800Z 37.5N  79.0W   30 KT  35 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 48H  30/0600Z 40.5N  67.5W   40 KT  45 MPH...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
 60H  30/1800Z...DISSIPATED
 
$$
Forecaster Brown
 
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/280900.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT3+shtml/280900.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Wind Speed Probabilities Number 16</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC WED OCT 28 2020                                              <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIAPWSAT3 ALL                                                  
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM                                                  
                                                                    
HURRICANE ZETA WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER  16                  
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL282020               
1500 UTC WED OCT 28 2020                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF HURRICANE ZETA WAS LOCATED NEAR LATITUDE 26.9
NORTH...LONGITUDE 91.7 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS NEAR 80 KTS
...90 MPH...150 KM/H.                                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z WED AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z WED 00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z THU 12Z THU 00Z FRI 12Z FRI 12Z SAT 12Z SUN 12Z MON
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
NANTUCKET MA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ATLANTIC CITY  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
DOVER DE       34  X   X( X)   7( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
ANNAPOLIS MD   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WASHINGTON DC  34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CAPE HENLOPEN  34  X   X( X)  14(14)   1(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
OCEAN CITY MD  34  X   X( X)  20(20)   1(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
PAX RIVER NAS  34  X   X( X)  15(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
WALLOPS CDA    34  X   X( X)  22(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
CHARLOTTESVIL  34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
RICHMOND VA    34  X   X( X)  20(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)   X(20)
 
DANVILLE VA    34  X   X( X)  22(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)   X(22)
 
NORFOLK NAS    34  X   X( X)  14(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)   X(14)
 
NORFOLK VA     34  X   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
OCEANA NAS VA  34  X   X( X)  10(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ELIZABETH CTY  34  X   X( X)   6( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
GREENSBORO NC  34  X   X( X)  23(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
RALEIGH NC     34  X   X( X)  13(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)   X(13)
 
ROCKY MT NC    34  X   X( X)   8( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
FAYETTEVILLE   34  X   X( X)   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
CHARLOTTE NC   34  X   2( 2)  14(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)   X(16)
 
COLUMBIA SC    34  X   3( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
ATLANTA GA     34  X  57(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)   X(57)
ATLANTA GA     50  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
AUGUSTA GA     34  X   5( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   4( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  2   6( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  1   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  4   5( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  4   2( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  5  10(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  7  42(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  1  53(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)   X(54)
COLUMBUS GA    50  X   3( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  2  47(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)   X(49)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  4  84(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)   X(88)
MONTGOMERY AL  50  X  27(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
MONTGOMERY AL  64  X   2( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)   X( 2)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34 11  66(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
WHITING FLD FL 50  1   7( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34 16  61(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
PENSACOLA FL   50  1   6( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34 15  11(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
MOBILE AL      34 72  26(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)   X(98)
MOBILE AL      50  3  59(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)   X(62)
MOBILE AL      64  X   9( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GULFPORT MS    34 96   4(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GULFPORT MS    50 52  28(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)   X(80)
GULFPORT MS    64  7  19(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)   X(26)
 
STENNIS MS     34 98   1(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
STENNIS MS     50 77   6(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
STENNIS MS     64 19   6(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)   X(25)
 
BURAS LA       34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
BURAS LA       50 86   1(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)   X(87)
BURAS LA       64 23   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)   X(23)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34 83   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)   X(83)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  4   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
JACKSON MS     34  6   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34 97   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)   X(97)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50 58   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)   X(58)
NEW ORLEANS LA 64  9   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34 99   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
GFMX 280N 910W 50 96   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)   X(96)
GFMX 280N 910W 64 17   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)   X(17)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34 27   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)   X(27)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34 52   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)   X(52)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  5   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  6   1( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
CAMERON LA     34  3   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
GALVESTON TX   34  2   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
PENSACOLA NAS  34 30  47(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)   X(77)
PENSACOLA NAS  50  2   5( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
KEESLER AB     34 94   6(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)   X(99)
KEESLER AB     50 41  40(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)   X(81)
KEESLER AB     64  4  17(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)   X(21)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER PASCH                                                    
NNNN                                                                
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 14:48:47 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT3+shtml/DDHHMM.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Wed, 28 Oct 2020 11:40:49 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL282020_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:25:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 11:40:49 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT28/AL2820_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:18:27 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:18:27 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?inundation">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/inundation_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta Link to Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Potential Storm Surge Flooding Map last updated Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:30:41 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:30:41 GMT</pubDate>
<validAdvisory>15</validAdvisory>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?inundation</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?inundation</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Hurricane Zeta Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?wsurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/images/wsurge_thumb.png"
alt="Hurricane Zeta Link to Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map"
width="60" height="48" /></a><br/>
Storm Surge Watch/Warning Map last updated Wed, 28 Oct 2020 08:57:16 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 08:57:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?wsurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at3+shtml/091827.shtml?wsurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Birmingham, AL</title>
<description>Issued at  417 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:17:56 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBMX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KBMX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Tallahassee, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  522 AM EDT Wed Oct 28 2020 /422 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020/</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:22:37 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KTAE.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Lake Charles, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  427 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:27:55 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLCH.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Mobile, AL / Pensacola, FL</title>
<description>Issued at  444 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:44:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KMOB.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Atlanta, GA</title>
<description>Issued at  557 AM EDT Wed Oct 28 2020</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 09:57:29 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KFFC.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS82-KFFC.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for New Orleans / Baton Rouge, LA</title>
<description>Issued at  705 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:05:40 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KLIX.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Local Statement for Jackson, MS</title>
<description>Issued at  810 AM CDT Wed Oct 28 2020</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 13:10:26 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/WTUS84-KJAN.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
