<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
   <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
   <description>Simulated NHC Forecast/Advisories</description>
   <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
   <copyright>2015 Jason Fleming</copyright>
   <managingEditor>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</managingEditor>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <webMaster>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</webMaster>
   <image>
      <url>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/seahorse.png</url>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
      <description>Seahorse</description>
      <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
      <width>96</width>
      <height>128</height>
   </image>
   <item>
      <title>Tropical Storm ISAIAS Forecast/Advisory Number 26</title>
      <description>Issued at 1500 UTC MON AUG 03 2020 <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM
 
TROPICAL STORM ISAIAS FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER  26
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL092020
1500 UTC MON AUG 03 2020
 
CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR PORTIONS OF THE PAMLICO 
AND ALBEMARLE SOUNDS...INCLUDING THE NEUSE AND PAMLICO RIVERS...
AND FOR THE NORTH CAROLINA OUTER BANKS FORM OREGON INLET TO THE 
NORTH CAROLINA/VIRGINIA BORDER.  
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS BEEN EXTENDED NORTHWARD TO THE MOUTH 
OF THE MERRIMACK RIVER...INCLUDING MARTHA'S VINEYARD...NANTUCKET... 
AND BLOCK ISLAND.
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR THE REMAINDER OF THE CHESAPEAKE BAY AND 
THE TIDAL POTOMAC RIVER NORTH OF COBB ISLAND HAS BEEN CHANGED TO A 
TROPICAL STORM WARNING.
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WATCH HAS BEEN EXTENDED NORTHWARD TO EASTPORT
MAINE.
 
THE TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS BEEN DISCONTINUED SOUTH OF ALTAMAHA
SOUND.
 
SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...

A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* EDISTO BEACH SOUTH CAROLINA TO CAPE FEAR NORTH CAROLINA
* PAMLICO AND ALBEMARLE SOUNDS, INCLUDING THE NEUSE AND PAMLICO 
RIVERS
* OREGON INLET NORTH CAROLINA TO THE NORTH CAROLINA/VIRGINIA BORDER
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* CAPE FEAR TO OREGON INLET NORTH CAROLINA
 
A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH CAROLINA TO SURF CITY NORTH CAROLINA
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALTAMAHA SOUND GEORGIA TO SOUTH SANTEE RIVER SOUTH CAROLINA
* NORTH OF SURF CITY NORTH CAROLINA TO THE MOUTH OF THE MERRIMACK
RIVER
* PAMLICO AND ALBEMARLE SOUNDS
* CHESAPEAKE BAY
* TIDAL POTOMAC RIVER
* DELAWARE BAY
* LONG ISLAND AND LONG ISLAND SOUND
* MARTHA'S VINEYARD...NANTUCKET...AND BLOCK ISLAND
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* MOUTH OF THE MERRIMACK RIVER TO EASTPORT MAINE
 
INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ALONG THE NORTHEAST COAST OF THE UNITED STATES
SHOULD MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ISAIAS.  ADDITIONAL WATCHES OR
WARNINGS MAY BE REQUIRED LATER TODAY.
 
A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING 
INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE IN 
THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION OF AREAS AT RISK...PLEASE 
SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC 
AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION.  PERSONS 
LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS TO 
PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR 
OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS. PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER 
INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL OFFICIALS.
 
A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS.
 
A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN 12 HOURS.
PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO
COMPLETION.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 36
HOURS.
 
A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.
 
TROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.7N  80.1W AT 03/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM
 
PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 360 DEGREES AT  11 KT
 
ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  998 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  60 KT WITH GUSTS TO  75 KT.
50 KT....... 50NE  50SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT.......100NE 110SE   0SW  60NW.
12 FT SEAS..150NE 120SE  60SW  90NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.
 
REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 30.7N  80.1W AT 03/1500Z
AT 03/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 30.2N  80.1W
 
FORECAST VALID 04/0000Z 33.1N  79.2W
MAX WIND  65 KT...GUSTS  80 KT.
64 KT... 25NE  25SE   0SW   0NW.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...100NE 120SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 04/1200Z 37.2N  77.0W...INLAND
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  70 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE   0SW  20NW.
34 KT...110NE 140SE   0SW  60NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/0000Z 42.0N  73.8W...INLAND
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT...  0NE  70SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...120NE 150SE   0SW  40NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 05/1200Z 46.7N  70.2W...INLAND
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...  0NE 170SE   0SW   0NW.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/0000Z 50.2N  67.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.
 
FORECAST VALID 06/1200Z 53.5N  64.2W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  25 KT...GUSTS  35 KT.
 
EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY
 
OUTLOOK VALID 07/1200Z...DISSIPATED
 
REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 30.7N  80.1W
 
INTERMEDIATE PUBLIC ADVISORY...WTNT34 KNHC/MIATCPAT4...AT 03/1800Z
 
NEXT ADVISORY AT 03/2100Z
 
$$
FORECASTER STEWART

</pre>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2020/09/26.092020.index-at.xml</link>
      <guid>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2020/09/26.092020.index-at.xml</guid>
      <author>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</author>
   </item>
</channel>
</rss>
