<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
   <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
   <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
   <description>Simulated NHC Forecast/Advisories</description>
   <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
   <copyright>2015 Jason Fleming</copyright>
   <managingEditor>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</managingEditor>
   <language>en-us</language>
   <webMaster>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</webMaster>
   <image>
      <url>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/seahorse.png</url>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/</link>
      <description>Seahorse</description>
      <title>Seahorse Coastal Consulting, LLC</title>
      <width>96</width>
      <height>128</height>
   </image>
   <item>
      <title>Hurricane MICHAEL Forecast/Advisory Number 9</title>
      <description>Issued at 2100 UTC MON OCT 08 2018 <![CDATA[<pre>
ZCZC MIATCMAT4 ALL
TTAA00 KNHC DDHHMM

HURRICANE MICHAEL FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   9
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL142018
2100 UTC MON OCT 08 2018

CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...

A STORM SURGE WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR THE GULF COAST OF FLORIDA
FROM THE OKALOOSA/WALTON COUNTY LINE TO ANCLOTE RIVER.

THE STORM SURGE WATCH HAS BEEN EXTENDED WEST OF NAVARRE FLORIDA TO
THE ALABAMA/FLORIDA BORDER.

A HURRICANE WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED FOR THE GULF COAST OF FLORIDA
FROM THE ALABAMA/FLORIDA BORDER EASTWARD TO SUWANNEE RIVER.

A HURRICANE WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FROM THE ALABAMA/FLORIDA BORDER
WESTWARD TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER.

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING HAS BEEN ISSUED FROM THE ALABAMA/FLORIDA
BORDER WESTWARD TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER AND FROM SUWANNEE
RIVER FLORIDA SOUTHWARD TO CHASSAHOWITZKA FLORIDA.

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH HAS BEEN ISSUED FROM THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA
BORDER WESTWARD TO THE MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...

A STORM SURGE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* OKALOOSA/WALTON COUNTY LINE FLORIDA TO ANCLOTE RIVER FLORIDA

A STORM SURGE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ANCLOTE RIVER FLORIDA TO ANNA MARIA ISLAND FLORIDA...INCLUDING
TAMPA BAY
* ALABAMA/FLORIDA BORDER TO OKALOOSA/WALTON COUNTY LINE FLORIDA

A HURRICANE WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALABAMA/FLORIDA BORDER TO SUWANNEE RIVER FLORIDA
* THE CUBAN PROVINCE OF PINAR DEL RIO

A HURRICANE WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALABAMA/FLORIDA BORDER TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* ALABAMA/FLORIDA BORDER TO THE MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER
* SUWANEE RIVER FLORIDA TO CHASSAHOWITZKA FLORIDA
* THE CUBAN PROVINCE OF THE ISLE OF YOUTH
* THE COAST OF MEXICO FROM TULUM TO CABO CATOCHE...INCLUDING
COZUMEL

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* CHASSAHOWITZKA TO ANNA MARIA ISLAND FLORIDA...INCLUDING TAMPA BAY
* MISSISSIPPI/ALABAMA BORDER TO THE MOUTH OF THE PEARL RIVER

A STORM SURGE WARNING MEANS THERE IS A DANGER OF LIFE-THREATENING
INUNDATION FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE COASTLINE...
DURING THE NEXT 36 HOURS IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS. FOR A DEPICTION
OF AREAS AT RISK PLEASE SEE THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE STORM SURGE
WATCH/WARNING GRAPHIC AVAILABLE AT HURRICANES.GOV.  THIS IS A
LIFE-THREATENING SITUATION.  PERSONS LOCATED WITHIN THESE AREAS
SHOULD TAKE ALL NECESSARY ACTIONS TO PROTECT LIFE AND PROPERTY FROM
RISING WATER AND THE POTENTIAL FOR OTHER DANGEROUS CONDITIONS.
PROMPTLY FOLLOW EVACUATION AND OTHER INSTRUCTIONS FROM LOCAL
OFFICIALS.

A HURRICANE WARNING MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE EXPECTED
SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA.  A WARNING IS TYPICALLY ISSUED
36 HOURS BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF
TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE
PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR DANGEROUS.  PREPARATIONS TO PROTECT LIFE
AND PROPERTY SHOULD BE RUSHED TO COMPLETION.

A TROPICAL STORM WARNING MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
EXPECTED SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE WARNING AREA WITHIN 36 HOURS.

A STORM SURGE WATCH MEANS THERE IS A POSSIBILITY OF LIFE-
THREATENING INUNDATION...FROM RISING WATER MOVING INLAND FROM THE
COASTLINE IN THE INDICATED LOCATIONS DURING THE NEXT 48 HOURS.

A HURRICANE WATCH MEANS THAT HURRICANE CONDITIONS ARE POSSIBLE
WITHIN THE WATCH AREA.  A WATCH IS TYPICALLY ISSUED 48 HOURS
BEFORE THE ANTICIPATED FIRST OCCURRENCE OF TROPICAL-STORM-FORCE
WINDS...CONDITIONS THAT MAKE OUTSIDE PREPARATIONS DIFFICULT OR
DANGEROUS.

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA GENERALLY WITHIN 48 HOURS.

INTERESTS ELSEWHERE ACROSS THE SOUTHEASTERN UNITED STATES SHOULD
MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF MICHAEL.

HURRICANE CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.2N  85.2W AT 08/2100Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  20 NM

PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH OR 355 DEGREES AT   8 KT

ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE  978 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  70 KT WITH GUSTS TO  85 KT.
64 KT....... 30NE   0SE   0SW  25NW.
50 KT....... 60NE  50SE  20SW  50NW.
34 KT.......120NE 150SE  80SW  90NW.
12 FT SEAS.. 90NE 150SE  60SW 240NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.

REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 22.2N  85.2W AT 08/2100Z
AT 08/1800Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 21.7N  85.1W

FORECAST VALID 09/0600Z 23.7N  85.7W
MAX WIND  85 KT...GUSTS 105 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  25SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 150SE  90SW 100NW.

FORECAST VALID 09/1800Z 25.7N  86.4W
MAX WIND  95 KT...GUSTS 115 KT.
64 KT... 30NE  30SE  20SW  25NW.
50 KT... 60NE  60SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 140SE  90SW 110NW.

FORECAST VALID 10/0600Z 27.9N  86.6W
MAX WIND 105 KT...GUSTS 130 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 70NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...130NE 140SE  90SW 120NW.

FORECAST VALID 10/1800Z 30.2N  85.8W...NEAR THE COAST
MAX WIND 100 KT...GUSTS 120 KT.
64 KT... 35NE  30SE  20SW  30NW.
50 KT... 50NE  70SE  40SW  50NW.
34 KT...100NE 140SE  90SW 100NW.

FORECAST VALID 11/1800Z 34.5N  80.5W...INLAND
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT... 70NE 140SE  50SW  50NW.

EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY

OUTLOOK VALID 12/1800Z 39.8N  68.8W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.

OUTLOOK VALID 13/1800Z 46.2N  50.0W...POST-TROP/EXTRATROP
MAX WIND  60 KT...GUSTS  75 KT.

REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 22.2N  85.2W

NEXT ADVISORY AT 09/0300Z

$$
FORECASTER BROWN

</pre>]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <link>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2018/14/09.142018.index-at.xml</link>
      <guid>http://www.seahorsecoastal.com/2018/14/09.142018.index-at.xml</guid>
      <author>jason.fleming@seahorsecoastal.com</author>
   </item>
</channel>
</rss>
