<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
 xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
 xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
 xmlns:gml="http://www.opengis.net/gml"
 xmlns:nhc="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov">
<channel>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 16:08:30 GMT</pubDate>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>Active tropical cyclones in the Atlantic, Caribbean, and the Gulf of Mexico</description>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<copyright>none</copyright>
<managingEditor>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</managingEditor>
<language>en-us</language>
<webMaster>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</webMaster>
<image>
<url>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gifs/xml_logo_nhc.gif</url>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/</link>
<title>NHC Atlantic</title>
<description>NOAA logo</description>
<width>95</width>
<height>45</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Atlantic Tropical Weather Outlook</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<br/>
000<br/>
ABNT20 KNHC 251603<br/>
TWOAT <br/>
<br/>
Special Tropical Weather Outlook<br/>
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL<br/>
1205 PM EDT Fri May 25 2018<br/>
<br/>
For the North Atlantic...Caribbean Sea and the Gulf of Mexico:<br/>
<br/>
The National Hurricane Center is issuing advisories on newly formed<br/>
Subtropical Storm Alberto, located over the northwestern Caribbean<br/>
Sea just east of the Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
Tropical cyclone formation is not expected during the next 5 days.<br/>
<br/>
Routine issuance of the Tropical Weather Outlook will resume on 1<br/>
June.<br/>
<br/>
&&<br/>
<br/>
Public Advisories on Alberto are issued under WMO header WTNT31 KNHC<br/>
and under AWIPS header MIATCPAT1.<br/>
Forecast/Advisories on Alberto are issued under WMO header WTNT21<br/>
KNHC and under AWIPS header MIATCMAT1.<br/>
<br/>
$$<br/>
Forecaster Stewart<br/>
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 16:03:16 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/gtwo.php?basin=atlc&amp;201805251603</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
 <title>Summary for Subtropical Storm Alberto (AT1/AL012018)</title>
 <guid isPermaLink="false">summary-al012018-201805251443</guid>
 <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:43:46 GMT</pubDate>
 <author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
 <link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/251443.shtml</link>
 <description>
  ...HEAVY RAINFALL EXPECTED TO AFFECT THE YUCATAN PENINSULA...WESTERN CUBA...FLORIDA...AND THE NORTHEASTERN GULF COAST THROUGH THE WEEKEND...
 As of 10:00 AM CDT Fri May 25
 the center of Alberto was located near 19.7, -86.8
 with movement NNE at 6 mph.
 The minimum central pressure was 1005 mb
 with maximum sustained winds of about 40 mph.
 </description>
 <nhc:Cyclone>
  <nhc:center>19.7, -86.8</nhc:center>
  <nhc:type>Subtropical Storm</nhc:type>
  <nhc:name>Alberto</nhc:name>
  <nhc:wallet>AT1</nhc:wallet>
  <nhc:atcf>AL012018</nhc:atcf>
  <nhc:datetime>10:00 AM CDT Fri May 25</nhc:datetime>
  <nhc:movement>NNE at 6 mph</nhc:movement>
  <nhc:pressure>1005 mb</nhc:pressure>
  <nhc:wind>40 mph</nhc:wind>
  <nhc:headline> ...HEAVY RAINFALL EXPECTED TO AFFECT THE YUCATAN PENINSULA...WESTERN CUBA...FLORIDA...AND THE NORTHEASTERN GULF COAST THROUGH THE WEEKEND...</nhc:headline>
 </nhc:Cyclone>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Alberto Public Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Fri May 25 2018  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT31 KNHC 251443
TCPAT1

BULLETIN
Subtropical Storm Alberto Advisory Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL012018
1000 AM CDT Fri May 25 2018

...PRE-SEASON SUBTROPICAL STORM ALBERTO FORMS OVER THE NORTHWESTERN
CARIBBEAN SEA...
...HEAVY RAINFALL EXPECTED TO AFFECT THE YUCATAN PENINSULA...WESTERN
CUBA...FLORIDA...AND THE NORTHEASTERN GULF COAST THROUGH THE
WEEKEND...


SUMMARY OF 1000 AM CDT...1500 UTC...INFORMATION
-----------------------------------------------
LOCATION...19.7N 86.8W
ABOUT 55 MI...90 KM S OF COZUMEL MEXICO
ABOUT 195 MI...315 KM SW OF THE WESTERN TIP OF CUBA
MAXIMUM SUSTAINED WINDS...40 MPH...65 KM/H
PRESENT MOVEMENT...NNE OR 20 DEGREES AT 6 MPH...9 KM/H
MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE...1005 MB...29.68 INCHES


WATCHES AND WARNINGS
--------------------
CHANGES WITH THIS ADVISORY:

The Government of Mexico has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for the
east coast of the Yucatan Peninsula from Tulum to Cabo Catoche.

The Government of Cuba has issued a Tropical Storm Watch for the
western Cuban province of Pinar del Rio.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT:

A Tropical Storm Watch is in effect for...
* Tulum to Cabo Catoche Mexico
* Cuban province of Pinar del Rio

A Tropical Storm Watch means that tropical storm conditions are
possible within the watch area, in this case within the next 24
hours.

Interests along the central and eastern U.S. Gulf Coast should
monitor the progress of Alberto. Tropical storm and storm surge
watches could be required for portions of this area later today or
tonight.

For storm information specific to your area, please monitor
products issued by your national meteorological service.


DISCUSSION AND OUTLOOK
----------------------
At 1000 AM CDT (1500 UTC), the center of Subtropical Storm Alberto
was located near latitude 19.7 North, longitude 86.8 West. The storm
is moving toward the north-northeast near 6 mph (9 km/h). A general
slow motion toward the north is expected through the weekend,
followed by a northwest turn by Monday. On the foreast track,
Alberto is expected to pass near the eastern coast of the Yucatan
peninsula tonight, be near the western tip of Cuba Saturday morning,
emerge over the southeastern Gulf of Mexico by Saturday night, and
approach the north-central Gulf Coast on Monday.

Maximum sustained winds are near 40 mph (65 km/h) with higher gusts.
Gradual strengthening is forecast for the next 72 hours.

Winds of 40 mph extend outward up to 115 miles (185 km) from the
center.

The estimated minimum central pressure is 1005 mb (29.68 inches).


HAZARDS AFFECTING LAND
----------------------
RAINFALL:  Alberto is expected to produce total rain accumulations
of 10 to 15 inches with isolated totals of 25 inches across the
northeastern portions of the Yucatan Peninsula and western Cuba.
These rains could produce life-threatening flash floods and
mudslides. Rainfall accmumulations of 4 to 8 inches with maximum
amounts of 12 inches are possible across the Florida Keys and
southern and southwestern Florida.  Heavy rain will likely begin
to affect the central Gulf Coast region and the southeastern Untied
States later this weekend and continue into early next week.
Flooding potential will increase across this region early next
week as Alberto is forecast to slow down after it moves inland.

WIND:  Tropical storm conditions are possible within the watch
area through Saturday.

SURF:  Swells generated by Alberto are affecting portions of
the coast of eastern Yucatan Peninsula and western Cuba.  These
swells are likely to cause life-threatening surf and rip current
conditions.  Hazardous surf conditions are likely to develop along
much of the central and eastern U.S. Gulf Coast this weekend. For
more information, consult products from your local weather office.


NEXT ADVISORY
-------------
Next intermediate advisory at 100 PM CDT.
Next complete advisory at 400 PM CDT.

$$
Forecaster Stewart

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:43:46 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/251443.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCPAT1+shtml/251443.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Alberto Forecast Advisory Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI MAY 25 2018  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT21 KNHC 251443
TCMAT1

SUBTROPICAL STORM ALBERTO FORECAST/ADVISORY NUMBER   1
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL012018
1500 UTC FRI MAY 25 2018

CHANGES IN WATCHES AND WARNINGS WITH THIS ADVISORY...

THE GOVERNMENT OF MEXICO HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR THE
EAST COAST OF THE YUCATAN PENINSULA FROM TULUM TO CABO CATOCHE.

THE GOVERNMENT OF CUBA HAS ISSUED A TROPICAL STORM WATCH FOR THE
WESTERN CUBAN PROVINCE OF PINAR DEL RIO.

SUMMARY OF WATCHES AND WARNINGS IN EFFECT...

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH IS IN EFFECT FOR...
* TULUM TO CABO CATOCHE MEXICO
* CUBAN PROVINCE OF PINAR DEL RIO

A TROPICAL STORM WATCH MEANS THAT TROPICAL STORM CONDITIONS ARE
POSSIBLE WITHIN THE WATCH AREA...IN THIS CASE WITHIN THE NEXT 24
HOURS.

INTERESTS ALONG THE CENTRAL AND EASTERN U.S. GULF COAST SHOULD
MONITOR THE PROGRESS OF ALBERTO. TROPICAL STORM AND STORM SURGE
WATCHES COULD BE REQUIRED FOR PORTIONS OF THIS AREA LATER TODAY OR
TONIGHT.

SUBTROPICAL STORM CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.7N  86.8W AT 25/1500Z
POSITION ACCURATE WITHIN  30 NM

PRESENT MOVEMENT TOWARD THE NORTH-NORTHEAST OR  20 DEGREES AT   5 KT

ESTIMATED MINIMUM CENTRAL PRESSURE 1005 MB
MAX SUSTAINED WINDS  35 KT WITH GUSTS TO  45 KT.
34 KT.......100NE 100SE   0SW   0NW.
WINDS AND SEAS VARY GREATLY IN EACH QUADRANT.  RADII IN NAUTICAL
MILES ARE THE LARGEST RADII EXPECTED ANYWHERE IN THAT QUADRANT.

REPEAT...CENTER LOCATED NEAR 19.7N  86.8W AT 25/1500Z
AT 25/1200Z CENTER WAS LOCATED NEAR 19.4N  87.0W

FORECAST VALID 26/0000Z 20.5N  86.6W
MAX WIND  35 KT...GUSTS  45 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE   0SW   0NW.

FORECAST VALID 26/1200Z 22.0N  86.2W
MAX WIND  40 KT...GUSTS  50 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE   0SW   0NW.

FORECAST VALID 27/0000Z 24.1N  85.8W
MAX WIND  45 KT...GUSTS  55 KT.
34 KT...100NE 100SE   0SW  60NW.

FORECAST VALID 27/1200Z 26.7N  86.1W
MAX WIND  50 KT...GUSTS  60 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE   0SW   0NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE   0SW  80NW.

FORECAST VALID 28/1200Z 29.3N  87.9W
MAX WIND  55 KT...GUSTS  65 KT.
50 KT... 50NE  50SE   0SW  40NW.
34 KT...100NE 100SE   0SW  80NW.

EXTENDED OUTLOOK. NOTE...ERRORS FOR TRACK HAVE AVERAGED NEAR 150 NM
ON DAY 4 AND 175 NM ON DAY 5...AND FOR INTENSITY NEAR 15 KT EACH DAY

OUTLOOK VALID 29/1200Z 31.0N  89.1W...INLAND
MAX WIND  30 KT...GUSTS  40 KT.

OUTLOOK VALID 30/1200Z 33.6N  88.7W...INLAND
MAX WIND  20 KT...GUSTS  30 KT.

REQUEST FOR 3 HOURLY SHIP REPORTS WITHIN 300 MILES OF 19.7N  86.8W

NEXT ADVISORY AT 25/2100Z

$$
FORECASTER STEWART


</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:43:14 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/251443.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCMAT1+shtml/251443.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Alberto Forecast Discussion Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1000 AM CDT Fri May 25 2018  <![CDATA[<pre>

000
WTNT41 KNHC 251444
TCDAT1

Subtropical Storm Alberto Discussion Number   1
NWS National Hurricane Center Miami FL       AL012018
1000 AM CDT Fri May 25 2018

The broad low pressure system that the NHC has been tracking for
the past several days over the Yucatan Peninsula has finally moved
offshore over the waters of the northwestern Caribbean Sea.
Although the system possesses multiple low-level circulations, the
overall larger circulation has improved since yesterday. Given that
the system has been interacting with a sharp upper-level trough,
the strongly sheared low has been designated a subtropical storm.
The initial intensity is based on buoy and ship observations of
30-35 kt. Ship 3ETA7 located just northeast of the center at 1100Z
reported 45-kt winds at 50 meters elevation. Those winds equate to
35-40 kt at 10 meters elevation. An Air Force Reserve Hurricane
Hunter Aircraft is scheduled to investigate Alberto later this
afternoon and provide more information on the storm's structure and
intensity.

The initial motion estimate is an uncertain 020/05 kt. The broad
inner-core wind field and multiple swirls makes the short-term
motion forecast a little tricky. However, a large subtropical ridge
to the east should generally induce a slow north to north-
northeastward motion for the next 24 hours or so. After that, the
ridge across the western Atlantic and Florida, along with a
mid/upper-level low forecast to develop over the central Gulf of
Mexico, should result in a faster northward motion at 36-48 hours,
followed by a gradual turn toward the northwest around the
northern fringe of the aforementioned mid/upper-level low. By 96
hours, the cyclone is forecast to slow down significantly as it
nears the north-central Gulf Coast due to a large weakness in the
subtropical ridge forecast to develop over the Deep South. The
official forecast track closely follows the consensus models TVCN
and HCCA.

Given the broad inner-core wind field and belligerent westerly wind
shear forecast to persist for the next 48 hours or so, only gradual
intensification is expected. By 72 hours, however, when the cyclone
is forecast to move slowly over above-normal SSTs of 28-29C and into
an upper-level col and weak wind shear, some additional
strengthening could occur. For now, the intensity forecast will
remain conservative due to possible intrusion of dry mid-level air
before landfall, and closely follows the HCCA consensus model.

KEY MESSAGES:

1. Regardless of its exact track and intensity, Alberto is expected
to produce heavy rainfall and flash flooding over the northeastern
Yucatan Peninsula of Mexico, western Cuba, southern Florida and the
Florida Keys. Rainfall and flooding potential will increase across
the central Gulf Coast region and the southeastern United States
later this weekend and early next week when Alberto is expected to
slow down after it moves inland.

2. Alberto could bring tropical storm conditions and storm surge to
portions of the central and eastern Gulf Coast later this weekend
and early next week, although it is too soon to specify the exact
location and magnitude of these impacts. Residents in these areas
should monitor the progress of Alberto, as tropical storm and storm
surge watches may be required later today or tonight.

3. Dangerous surf and rip current conditions are affecting portions
of the Yucatan Peninsula and western Cuba and will likely spread
along the eastern and central U.S. Gulf Coast later this weekend.

FORECAST POSITIONS AND MAX WINDS

INIT  25/1500Z 19.7N  86.8W   35 KT  40 MPH
 12H  26/0000Z 20.5N  86.6W   35 KT  40 MPH
 24H  26/1200Z 22.0N  86.2W   40 KT  45 MPH
 36H  27/0000Z 24.1N  85.8W   45 KT  50 MPH
 48H  27/1200Z 26.7N  86.1W   50 KT  60 MPH
 72H  28/1200Z 29.3N  87.9W   55 KT  65 MPH
 96H  29/1200Z 31.0N  89.1W   30 KT  35 MPH...INLAND
120H  30/1200Z 33.6N  88.7W   20 KT  25 MPH...INLAND

$$
Forecaster Stewart

</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:44:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/251444.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIATCDAT1+shtml/251444.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Alberto Wind Speed Probabilities Number 1</title>
<description>Issued at 1500 UTC FRI MAY 25 2018                                              <![CDATA[<pre>

000
FONT11 KNHC 251444
PWSAT1
                                                                    
SUBTROPICAL STORM ALBERTO WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES NUMBER   1       
NWS NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER MIAMI FL       AL012018               
1500 UTC FRI MAY 25 2018                                            
                                                                    
AT 1500Z THE CENTER OF SUBTROPICAL STORM ALBERTO WAS LOCATED NEAR   
LATITUDE 19.7 NORTH...LONGITUDE 86.8 WEST WITH MAXIMUM SUSTAINED    
WINDS NEAR 35 KTS...40 MPH...65 KM/H.                               
                                                                    
Z INDICATES COORDINATED UNIVERSAL TIME (GREENWICH)                  
   ATLANTIC STANDARD TIME (AST)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   EASTERN  DAYLIGHT TIME (EDT)...SUBTRACT 4 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
   CENTRAL  DAYLIGHT TIME (CDT)...SUBTRACT 5 HOURS FROM Z TIME      
                                                                    
WIND SPEED PROBABILITY TABLE FOR SPECIFIC LOCATIONS                 
                                                                    
CHANCES OF SUSTAINED (1-MINUTE AVERAGE) WIND SPEEDS OF AT LEAST     
   ...34 KT (39 MPH... 63 KM/H)...                                  
   ...50 KT (58 MPH... 93 KM/H)...                                  
   ...64 KT (74 MPH...119 KM/H)...                                  
FOR LOCATIONS AND TIME PERIODS DURING THE NEXT 5 DAYS               
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES FOR LOCATIONS ARE GIVEN AS OP(CP) WHERE               
    OP  IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT BEGINNING DURING            
        AN INDIVIDUAL TIME PERIOD (ONSET PROBABILITY)               
   (CP) IS THE PROBABILITY OF THE EVENT OCCURRING BETWEEN           
        12Z FRI AND THE FORECAST HOUR (CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY)      
                                                                    
PROBABILITIES ARE GIVEN IN PERCENT                                  
X INDICATES PROBABILITIES LESS THAN 1 PERCENT                       
PROBABILITIES FOR 34 KT AND 50 KT ARE SHOWN AT A GIVEN LOCATION WHEN
THE 5-DAY CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 3 PERCENT.             
PROBABILITIES FOR 34...50...64 KT SHOWN WHEN THE 5-DAY              
64-KT CUMULATIVE PROBABILITY IS AT LEAST 1 PERCENT.                 
                                                                    
                                                                    
  - - - - WIND SPEED PROBABILITIES FOR SELECTED LOCATIONS - - - -   
                                                                    
               FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM    FROM 
  TIME       12Z FRI 00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE
PERIODS         TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO      TO  
             00Z SAT 12Z SAT 00Z SUN 12Z SUN 12Z MON 12Z TUE 12Z WED
                                                                    
FORECAST HOUR    (12)   (24)    (36)    (48)    (72)    (96)   (120)
- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - 
LOCATION       KT                                                   
                                                                    
ATLANTA GA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
KINGS BAY GA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)   X( 4)
 
WAYCROSS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   4( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)
 
MAYPORT NS FL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
JACKSONVILLE   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)   X( 5)
 
GAINESVILLE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   6(10)   1(11)   X(11)
 
DAYTONA BEACH  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
THE VILLAGES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   X(10)   X(10)
 
ORLANDO FL     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   X( 7)   X( 7)
 
COCOA BEACH FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
PATRICK AFB    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
FT PIERCE FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
W PALM BEACH   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
FT LAUDERDALE  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MIAMI FL       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
HOMESTEAD ARB  34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)   X( 3)
 
MARATHON FL    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)   X( 5)
 
KEY WEST FL    34  X   1( 1)   3( 4)   3( 7)   1( 8)   X( 8)   X( 8)
 
NAPLES FL      34  X   X( X)   3( 3)   5( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)   X( 9)
 
FT MYERS FL    34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   6( 8)   3(11)   X(11)   X(11)
 
VENICE FL      34  X   X( X)   2( 2)   9(11)   4(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
TAMPA FL       34  X   X( X)   1( 1)   9(10)   5(15)   X(15)   X(15)
 
CEDAR KEY FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   8(16)   1(17)   X(17)
 
TALLAHASSEE FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  14(19)   2(21)   X(21)
 
ST MARKS FL    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  15(21)   2(23)   X(23)
 
APALACHICOLA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)  26(35)   2(37)   1(38)
APALACHICOLA   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   5( 6)   1( 7)   X( 7)
APALACHICOLA   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   X( 1)
 
GFMX 290N 850W 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  16(17)  25(42)   2(44)   X(44)
GFMX 290N 850W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   7( 8)   X( 8)   1( 9)
GFMX 290N 850W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)
 
PANAMA CITY FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)  28(36)   4(40)   1(41)
PANAMA CITY FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)
PANAMA CITY FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
DESTIN EXEC AP 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)  30(35)   6(41)   1(42)
DESTIN EXEC AP 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   1(11)
DESTIN EXEC AP 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
COLUMBUS GA    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   3(10)   1(11)
 
BIRMINGHAM AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   3( 7)   2( 9)
 
MONTGOMERY AL  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  11(11)   4(15)   1(16)
 
WHITING FLD FL 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  28(31)   8(39)   2(41)
WHITING FLD FL 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   3( 9)   1(10)
WHITING FLD FL 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   X( 2)
 
PENSACOLA FL   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)  32(35)   9(44)   1(45)
PENSACOLA FL   50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   4(12)   1(13)
PENSACOLA FL   64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
GFMX 290N 870W 34  X   X( X)   1( 1)  12(13)  39(52)   4(56)   1(57)
GFMX 290N 870W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)   3(19)   X(19)
GFMX 290N 870W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   1( 5)   1( 6)
 
MOBILE AL      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  25(27)  14(41)   2(43)
MOBILE AL      50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   1(11)
MOBILE AL      64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)   1( 2)
 
GULFPORT MS    34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  24(25)  14(39)   3(42)
GULFPORT MS    50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   5(10)   1(11)
GULFPORT MS    64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
STENNIS MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  19(20)  14(34)   3(37)
STENNIS MS     50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   4( 4)   5( 9)   1(10)
STENNIS MS     64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   X( 2)
 
BURAS LA       34  X   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)  24(26)  12(38)   2(40)
BURAS LA       50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   6(12)   1(13)
BURAS LA       64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
GFMX 280N 890W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)  24(30)   6(36)   1(37)
GFMX 280N 890W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   9( 9)   3(12)   X(12)
GFMX 280N 890W 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   X( 3)   1( 4)
 
JACKSON MS     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   5( 5)   7(12)   3(15)
 
NEW ORLEANS LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  15(16)  11(27)   2(29)
NEW ORLEANS LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   X( 7)
NEW ORLEANS LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)
 
GFMX 280N 910W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)  10(11)   5(16)   1(17)
GFMX 280N 910W 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   X( 4)
 
BATON ROUGE LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   8( 8)   9(17)   2(19)
BATON ROUGE LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   1( 2)   1( 3)
 
MORGAN CITY LA 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)  10(10)   8(18)   2(20)
MORGAN CITY LA 50  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   3( 4)   1( 5)
MORGAN CITY LA 64  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   X( 1)
 
ALEXANDRIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   4( 7)   1( 8)
 
LAFAYETTE LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   6( 6)   6(12)   1(13)
 
NEW IBERIA LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   7( 7)   6(13)   2(15)
 
GFMX 280N 930W 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
SHREVEPORT LA  34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   1( 3)
 
FORT POLK LA   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   2( 2)   3( 5)   1( 6)
 
LAKE CHARLES   34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
CAMERON LA     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   3( 3)   3( 6)   1( 7)
 
JASPER TX      34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
KOUNTZE TX     34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
PORT ARTHUR TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   1( 4)
 
HIGH ISLAND TX 34  X   X( X)   X( X)   X( X)   1( 1)   2( 3)   X( 3)
 
COZUMEL MX     34 35   5(40)   1(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)   X(41)
 
CP SAN ANTONIO 34  7  36(43)   8(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)   X(51)
CP SAN ANTONIO 50  X   2( 2)   2( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)   X( 4)
 
HAVANA         34  X   2( 2)   4( 6)   2( 8)   X( 8)   1( 9)   X( 9)
 
ISLE OF PINES  34  1   2( 3)   2( 5)   1( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)   X( 6)
 
$$                                                                  
FORECASTER STEWART                                                  
</pre>]]></description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:44:13 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/251444.shtml</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/text/refresh/MIAPWSAT1+shtml/251444.shtml</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Alberto Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/152536.shtml?cone">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT01/AL012018_5day_cone_with_line_and_wind_sm2.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Alberto 5-Day Uncertainty Track Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
5-Day Uncertainty Track last updated Fri, 25 May 2018 14:45:41 GMT
<br /><br /><a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/152536.shtml?tswind120">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT01/AL012018_wind_probs_34_F120_sm2.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Alberto 34-Knot Wind Speed Probabilities"
width="500" height="400" /> </a><br/>
Wind Speed Probabilities last updated Fri, 25 May 2018 15:25:26 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 14:45:41 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/152536.shtml?cone</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/152536.shtml?cone</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
<item>
<title>Subtropical Storm Alberto Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics</title>
<description>
<![CDATA[
<a href="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/152536.shtml?gm_psurge">
<img src="https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/storm_graphics/AT01/AL0118_psurge2_m1_sm2.png"
alt="Subtropical Storm Alberto Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics Image"
width="500" height="400" /></a><br/>
Probabilistic Storm Surge Graphics last updated Fri, 25 May 2018 15:25:36 GMT
]]>
</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 15:25:36 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/152536.shtml?gm_psurge</link>
<guid>https://www.nhc.noaa.gov/refresh/graphics_at1+shtml/152536.shtml?gm_psurge</guid>
<author>nhcwebmaster@noaa.gov (NHC Webmaster)</author>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
